2
00:00:00:16 --> 00:00:06:00
Yeah, with this project it’s not like a film or a book where you just consume it and you’ve got it and you walk away. 

3
00:00:06:03 --> 00:00:08:28
 This is like getting lost in a forest, quite literally.  

4
00:00:09:01 --> 00:00:12:25
You’re wandering around, you’re collecting this story, and looking at that story, and

5
00:00:12:28 --> 00:00:15:12
 I think the entirety of it is well beyond your grasp, 

6
00:00:15:15 --> 00:00:19:06
which is kind of a nice experience to have.

