2
00:00:00:14 --> 00:00:04:21
I lead a small team at Google called the Data Arts team.  It’s part of the creative lab.

3
00:00:04:24 --> 00:00:09:13
  We basically just get to make really fun experiments and art projects that push the technology forward.

