2
00:00:01:07 --> 00:00:07:06
It’s funny because I grew up with computer games, and I think
I still totally enjoy and love playing computer games,

3
00:00:07:09 --> 00:00:12:16
but at some point, I started to realize that a lot of the 
interfaces and experiences that I was loving from games

4
00:00:12:19 --> 00:00:15:01
were also applying to other aspects of my life, 

5
00:00:15:04 --> 00:00:18:26
and I think there is a really interesting interplay between

6
00:00:18:29 --> 00:00:22:20
 useful interface and cultural object and game play.

7
00:00:22:23 --> 00:00:27:25
  I think where all those things meet is really ripe for exploration, and I think

8
00:00:27:28 --> 00:00:31:22
 throughout history, our lives have been rich experiences 

9
00:00:31:25 --> 00:00:34:25
just intrinsically because we live in the natural world,

10
00:00:34:28 --> 00:00:37:25
 and I think something happens when you take things digital 

11
00:00:37:28 --> 00:00:43:21
where oftentimes the context gets stripped down and it becomes numbers and text on a clean plain page. 

12
00:00:43:24 --> 00:00:46:15
 I think there is a lot of room for us to explore and take, 

13
00:00:46:18 --> 00:00:50:17
kind of re-embody those experiences to make those culturally interesting again

14
00:00:50:20 --> 00:00:55:21
 and make them experiences not just kind of extracting text and data.

