2
00:00:01:00 --> 00:00:05:19
And when we create these little brain systems, if you will, they have these amazing attributes.  

3
00:00:05:22 --> 00:00:11:09
They have perfect memories.  They have the ability to communicate across the planet, and 

4
00:00:11:19 --> 00:00:14:02
they are also incredibly smart. 

5
00:00:14:05 --> 00:00:16:23
 Despite the fact that they don’t have any creativity to speak of, 

6
00:00:16:26 --> 00:00:20:21
they are incredibly fast at doing certain types of calculations

