2
00:00:01:07 --> 00:00:05:15
So, this project was really kind of a lucid dream.  You are moving from one world to another 

3
00:00:05:18 --> 00:00:08:10
and eventually you enter this landscape that 

4
00:00:08:13 --> 00:00:12:05
is inhabited by all these strange creations created from people across the planet. 

5
00:00:12:08 --> 00:00:16:11
 There is a voxel creator which is basically like legos in 3D 

6
00:00:16:14 --> 00:00:20:10
and people are building their own models that then get cast into this desert landscape.

