2
00:00:01:01 --> 00:00:06:29
Things don’t look as beautiful as they could look in a research paper.

3
00:00:07:02 --> 00:00:11:26
It’s like because there is a comfort with actually…

4
00:00:11:29 --> 00:00:18:11
the goal of a scientist is, okay, I want to get this result out, I want to publish this paper, so

5
00:00:19:18 --> 00:00:24:28
there is not much focus or so much interest in making something that is

6
00:00:25:01 --> 00:00:29:08
aesthetically more beautiful.  I just want to represent this

7
00:00:29:11 --> 00:00:34:10
at the minimal level that I need to, so I can convey the message.

