2
00:00:00:28 --> 00:00:04:14
Not only to say, well, we just want to make this prettier,

3
00:00:04:17 --> 00:00:08:26
I mean, because we just want to have nicer figures or just a nicer looking tool, but

4
00:00:09:00 --> 00:00:14:24
I think it’s like this idea like in mathematics

5
00:00:15:13 --> 00:00:20:04
typically the equations that are correct are also beautiful.

