2
00:00:00:23 --> 00:00:06:01
…I spent about a decade exploring, doing many different media,

3
00:00:06:04 --> 00:00:10:11
doing installations, doing printed work, doing a little bit of fabricated

4
00:00:10:14 --> 00:00:13:19
work as well and collaborating with architects, collaborating with fashion designers,

5
00:00:13:22 --> 00:00:16:29
and what I have learned from that is that software is what I love the most.

