2
00:00:00:28 --> 00:00:03:20
I can’t really yet imagine what this new model of 

3
00:00:03:23 --> 00:00:09:16
it’s not cinema, it’s not a game, and it’s also not an abstract visual,

4
00:00:09:21 --> 00:00:14:22
but it’s somehow puts them together into something that’s totally engrossing.

