2
00:00:00:29 --> 00:00:05:01
What I knew and what I wanted to know suddenly became really clear,

3
00:00:05:04 --> 00:00:08:10
and so I started learning the program when I was about 26 or 27,

4
00:00:08:14 --> 00:00:13:01
and then I really learned when I got to the Aesthetics and Computation Group and started

5
00:00:13:04 --> 00:00:16:01
learning from Golan and Ben and other people there.

