2
00:00:00:27 --> 00:00:06:16
I'm fascinated and inspired by nature, but I have never tried to or attempted to recreate it.

3
00:00:07:00 --> 00:00:11:06
For me, it’s always been about developing my own microworld from the ground up.

4
00:00:11:20 --> 00:00:17:10
It’s basically an abstraction of how nature works rather than trying to be an artificial nature.

