2
00:00:01:06 --> 00:00:04:24
It was really just seeing people do extraordinary work with it

3
00:00:04:27 --> 00:00:10:15
and really pushing the software to do things that were sort of beyond our expectations of what it could do.

