2
00:00:01:16 --> 00:00:08:10
You need to have a little bit of a noise in the system in order to give it an organic quality.

3
00:00:08:13 --> 00:00:14:06
It’s essential to that, because if you are simulating anything …and in my case, I am not really simulating something specific,

4
00:00:14:09 --> 00:00:19:12
I am more sort of simulating something artificial or simulating something I have imagined…

5
00:00:21:20 --> 00:00:28:18
any given number of parameters isn’t enough to sort of fully exhaust the boundaries,

6
00:00:28:21 --> 00:00:35:08
and so by adding a little bit of noise into it, you are able to sort of coax other forms to emerge from it.

