2
00:00:01:18 --> 00:00:04:23
I don’t know what I’d do in the end.  I mean, my process is always to experiment,

3
00:00:04:26 --> 00:00:09:22
it’s always to try out a few different things and see what I think is most engaging and to kind of follow a tree,

4
00:00:09:25 --> 00:00:15:09
so whenever I make anything, it’s always about branching off and branching off and branching off and then gradually

5
00:00:15:21 --> 00:00:22:24
selecting from that. Like, I try and make things instead of cutting off ideas before I see them made physical,

6
00:00:22:27 --> 00:00:29:12
so I react to things physically with sight and sound and body and make decisions from that

7
00:00:29:15 --> 00:00:35:17
rather than trying to sort of not follow an idea because I think it might not work out.

