2
00:00:00:28 --> 00:00:06:13
I think the most simple like visual example is birds flocking or fish schooling

3
00:00:06:16 --> 00:00:10:19
where each fish is its own autonomous sort of animal

4
00:00:10:22 --> 00:00:17:05
and they have a few basic sort of guidelines that they follow where they try and stay away from others,

5
00:00:17:08 --> 00:00:22:27
they try and move in the same direction, and as a result of all of that, these basic behaviors of these creatures,

6
00:00:23:00 --> 00:00:29:10
you see these extraordinary sort of secondary forms. The flock from the individuals begin to emerge.

