2
00:00:00:27 --> 00:00:03:18
…How you build things that are creative coder are really different from how you build things

3
00:00:03:21 --> 00:00:08:00
in the more classic computer science way where you plan first and then build.

4
00:00:08:03 --> 00:00:11:12
So this idea that we have really promoted with Processing of sketching with code,

5
00:00:11:15 --> 00:00:15:18
I think is the predominant thing that I learned there which is really a design process,

6
00:00:15:21 --> 00:00:19:19
that you think through doing and you learn and you develop through making.

