2
00:00:01:07 --> 00:00:04:14
People often think that understanding a 3D world

3
00:00:04:17 --> 00:00:08:07
and seeing a 3D world are naturally the same thing,

4
00:00:08:10 --> 00:00:14:15
and I think there is a distinction there which needs to be identified by any artist who works with 3D media.

5
00:00:15:12 --> 00:00:18:09
People understand 3D.  They understand that if they move their head left,

6
00:00:18:12 --> 00:00:22:02
the thing behind might come into view, and if they move their head right again, it might go back out of view. 

7
00:00:22:22 --> 00:00:26:24
Now, does that mean that we can see in 3D?

8
00:00:27:07 --> 00:00:33:23
 I think that we, of course, from our point of view can point 

9
00:00:34:04 --> 00:00:37:26
and in order to point we are defining a 2D direction away from us, 

10
00:00:38:29 --> 00:00:42:23
and down that direction is something that we can see, 

11
00:00:42:29 --> 00:00:45:03
and this happens across our entire vision.

12
00:00:46:14 --> 00:00:50:29
Now, this defines everything that we can see. 

13
00:00:51:02 --> 00:00:55:08
 We can define everything that we can see in 2D as a 2D map.

14
00:00:56:02 --> 00:01:01:01
For every position, we might be able to know more about it like how far away it is, which object does it belong to, 

15
00:01:01:04 --> 00:01:03:22
only to the things which are intelligent which involve understanding the world,

16
00:01:03:25 --> 00:01:08:20
but our sight in itself is a 2D faculty. 

17
00:01:08:23 --> 00:01:11:11
We see surfaces.  We have line of sight. 

18
00:01:11:14 --> 00:01:16:12
We have a position for the world out from which we observe the world. 

19
00:01:16:29 --> 00:01:20:09
We are 3D beings in a 3D world

20
00:01:20:14 --> 00:01:22:22
and therefore, we must see in 2D, 

21
00:01:22:25 --> 00:01:26:23
the same way that a 2D being in a 2D world must see in one dimension.

