2
00:00:01:00 --> 00:00:03:11
Again, this was back in 2003.  

3
00:00:03:14 --> 00:00:07:19
You had to explain to people what wikis were, how they worked,

4
00:00:07:22 --> 00:00:13:13
 and the fact that Wikipedia was being created by a multitude of authors,

5
00:00:13:16 --> 00:00:17:03
so this visualization made these things very, very clear.

