2
00:00:01:04 --> 00:00:03:21
Another visualization we did Google Plus Ripples. 

3
00:00:03:24 --> 00:00:06:01
We were confronted exactly with that question,

4
00:00:06:04 --> 00:00:11:15
how do you show how things go viral on a social network? 

5
00:00:11:18 --> 00:00:16:02
We chose to show, okay, if you have a URL that everybody is sharing

6
00:00:16:05 --> 00:00:21:04
and talking about how do you show the path, the flow of this URL,

7
00:00:21:22 --> 00:00:27:12
and the first thing we thought about was can we visualize this as a tree?

8
00:00:27:15 --> 00:00:31:25
 I share it with you, you share it with your friends, your friends share it, that’s a tree,

9
00:00:31:28 --> 00:00:33:10
okay, let’s do that.

10
00:00:33:15 --> 00:00:36:20
It didn’t work, obviously,

11
00:00:36:23 --> 00:00:40:29
because these things have exponential growth

12
00:00:41:02 --> 00:00:43:23
and so the tree had a huge breadth

13
00:00:43:26 --> 00:00:49:23
and you could not read any of the labels, 

14
00:00:49:26 --> 00:00:53:00
so you couldn’t see who was sharing things with whom.

15
00:00:54:07 --> 00:01:00:25
Now we could have continued with that visualization and said, well, that’s what it looks like, that’s the spread, that’s something going viral,

16
00:01:01:08 --> 00:01:06:17
but we weren’t happy with that.  We decided no, you have to be able to read people’s names.

