2
00:00:00:28 --> 00:00:06:12
We were interested in understanding how people were working together

3
00:00:06:15 --> 00:00:11:05
on Wikipedia to create these very sophisticated articles, 

4
00:00:11:08 --> 00:00:15:20
and we were interested in patterns of collaboration,

5
00:00:15:23 --> 00:00:21:14
 so for instance, were people fighting, and if they were fighting, how were they resolving their fights?

6
00:00:21:17 --> 00:00:25:14
how were people deciding what piece of content

7
00:00:25:17 --> 00:00:29:00
belonged in a certain page or in a different page?

