2
00:00:00:13 --> 00:00:04:11
So, it’s sort of an unintuitive leap of faith

3
00:00:04:20 --> 00:00:08:17
that complexity can actually help

4
00:00:08:20 --> 00:00:10:22
make things easier to understand,

5
00:00:10:25 --> 00:00:16:12
 but I think if done right, complexity is very important 

6
00:00:16:15 --> 00:00:20:24
to understanding the kinds of data that we deal with.

