2
00:00:01:13 --> 00:00:03:10
What is data, how do you define data,

3
00:00:03:13 --> 00:00:05:00
and how do you capture things

4
00:00:05:03 --> 00:00:09:11
that you wouldn’t even think of as data necessarily?

