2
00:00:01:14 --> 00:00:04:15
It’s a thrill for us, as makers,

3
00:00:04:18 --> 00:00:05:28
because 

4
00:00:06:28 --> 00:00:11:10
I think that if I make exactly what I imagined it would be a little boring.

