2
00:00:00:28 --> 00:00:05:07
I mean, I am inspired by a quote from Jackson Pollock I believe where he says,

3
00:00:05:10 --> 00:00:09:03
make a mark, look at it, respond to it by making a mark,

4
00:00:09:07 --> 00:00:13:08
look at it, respond to it, evaluate it, and this is, kind of,

5
00:00:13:11 --> 00:00:19:07
I don’t think it’s wrong to call it an improvisatory way of working.

