2
00:00:01:01 --> 00:00:03:24
You know if I have a huge dataset and I want to visualize it,

3
00:00:03:27 --> 00:00:08:12
 I am not going to draw something by hand, I'm going to 

4
00:00:08:17 --> 00:00:11:01
put them in the computer and do something with code.

