2
00:00:01:06 --> 00:00:03:15
I chose math at the university 

3
00:00:03:18 --> 00:00:07:04
because I had no idea what I was going to do when I grew up 

4
00:00:07:07 --> 00:00:11:24
and it was hard and I liked that it was hard, but I could figure it out

