2
00:00:00:29 --> 00:00:03:25
There is an over-reliance of data as truth 

3
00:00:03:28 --> 00:00:07:27
and maybe an under-reliance on memory as truth and I think that’s 

4
00:00:09:02 --> 00:00:12:17
both things can be 

5
00:00:12:29 --> 00:00:16:27
true and false to the same extent actually.

