2
00:00:01:15 --> 00:00:05:24
You can mathematically model in general what’s going to be happening, but then

3
00:00:05:27 --> 00:00:10:23
 every now and then you would get some just completely crazy vortex coming through, and 

4
00:00:10:26 --> 00:00:14:09
you could see, we had like 3 months of data, 

5
00:00:14:12 --> 00:00:18:11
and there are these very specific events that come through that you could never predict, 

6
00:00:18:14 --> 00:00:23:05
so you know you can do that sort of prediction on average it’s going to be this, 

7
00:00:23:08 --> 00:00:26:03
but then you have these sudden events, 

8
00:00:26:06 --> 00:00:29:19
this sort of complexity, right, these sudden events who knows what it came from and 

9
00:00:29:22 --> 00:00:33:28
you have a vortex going through totally unpredictable.

