2
00:00:01:04 --> 00:00:04:18
But then that doesn’t quite catch the

3
00:00:04:25 --> 00:00:07:14
freedom that I want people to have in it, so maybe like a 

4
00:00:07:18 --> 00:00:11:00
data choose-your-own-adventure essay or something like this.

