2
00:00:01:00 --> 00:00:04:20
I sort of liked it it follows rules, but those rules are human created. 

3
00:00:04:23 --> 00:00:09:01
 I sort of like the idea that it could be anything else like we have this math and 

4
00:00:09:04 --> 00:00:12:13
we use it because it sort of describes the world well, but 

5
00:00:12:16 --> 00:00:16:24
you can imagine having somehow created a different mathematics

