2
00:00:00:29 --> 00:00:04:06
It’s like a struggle I'm literally right in the middle of, right now.

3
00:00:04:09 --> 00:00:07:23
Am I going to keep trying to code this stuff myself or am I going to

4
00:00:07:27 --> 00:00:10:25
 sort of back off, have ideas,

5
00:00:10:28 --> 00:00:15:29
do design, and bring in other people to do the coding, and like I'm right in the middle of it, so 

6
00:00:16:08 --> 00:00:17:03
  I don’t know!

