2
00:00:01:03 --> 00:00:03:22
If I want to make the cave open,

3
00:00:05:02 --> 00:00:06:16
 but in a way

4
00:00:06:29 --> 00:00:09:12
that makes people want to look around, 

5
00:00:09:15 --> 00:00:11:19
so maybe that gives people

6
00:00:13:16 --> 00:00:14:27
some leads,

7
00:00:15:06 --> 00:00:18:10
so that they are not just blind in there

