2
00:00:01:01 --> 00:00:05:10
I personally have had immersive experiences with data, because I 

3
00:00:06:16 --> 00:00:07:18
have

4
00:00:07:28 --> 00:00:11:16
 the tools and the skills to spend the time looking into it, 

5
00:00:11:19 --> 00:00:16:21
so maybe part of what I want to do is make that possible for other people,

 yeah.

