2
00:00:00:10 --> 00:00:05:14
It’s I mean, I just think the often the truth that we show with data is 

3
00:00:05:24 --> 00:00:10:05
so simplified, like removes so much of the complexity, as to actually be false.

