2
00:00:01:06 --> 00:00:05:05
I don’t love the experience of writing code. 

3
00:00:05:13 --> 00:00:08:00
 I would rather not honestly, but 

4
00:00:08:04 --> 00:00:11:09
there are these questions and that’s the way to solve them 

5
00:00:11:12 --> 00:00:13:25
and so that’s what compels me.

