2
00:00:00:27 --> 00:00:04:05
We are making these interactive tools and I fail to believe 

3
00:00:04:08 --> 00:00:07:24
that people are actually interacting with them

for very long, 

4
00:00:07:27 --> 00:00:11:28
and I would like to make things that people really want to

5
00:00:12:01 --> 00:00:14:01
go deep into.

