2
00:00:01:05 --> 00:00:03:29
I started as a generative artist,

3
00:00:04:02 --> 00:00:08:14
and I did software-based work that was contained in its own system.

4
00:00:08:17 --> 00:00:12:07
Robert was talking about, in his talk, you know, floating in a black space.

5
00:00:12:10 --> 00:00:15:25
That was exactly what I did for a decade,

6
00:00:16:14 --> 00:00:19:20
 and I still love that kind of work and I still do that kind of work.

7
00:00:19:23 --> 00:00:23:27
People just don’t pay attention to it, because it’s not the work that I am most well known for

8
00:00:24:04 --> 00:00:25:28
which I kind of love.  I love that.

