2
00:00:01:10 --> 00:00:06:27
So I would love to see a world where people like Karsten Schmidt are paid well to



3
00:00:07:00 --> 00:00:10:28
to share their wisdom and to do workshops,



4
00:00:11:01 --> 00:00:12:04
and I think

5
00:00:12:12 --> 00:00:17:21
that’s something that people maybe should keep in mind. These people that


6
00:00:17:24 --> 00:00:22:05
like Karsten who are largely doing all this work completely uncompensated,

7
00:00:23:18 --> 00:00:27:22
buy their books,



8
00:00:27:27 --> 00:00:32:22
and do those things that, bring them into your company to speak, because that’s like something that

9
00:00:34:07 --> 00:00:36:12
– yeah, he’s

10
00:00:37:10 --> 00:00:38:19
 a machine, right?

11
00:00:38:22 --> 00:00:41:19
I don’t even understand how he functions.

12
00:00:41:28 --> 00:00:48:00
He is like on another plane of reality for me as far as programming goes.  I start to look at him 

13
00:00:48:05 --> 00:00:52:02
him and Andrew Bell and all these guys who are like, 

14
00:00:52:05 --> 00:00:54:27
I don’t even – I don’t know where they are….

