2
00:00:01:06 --> 00:00:06:14
I’m on this list-serve for code artists, and each one of them has this like amazing solo repetition, like 

3
00:00:06:17 --> 00:00:10:11
wow, Robert Hodgin, Joshua Davis, 

4
00:00:10:23 --> 00:00:14:27
Zach Lieberman, Theo Watson, you know and

5
00:00:16:20 --> 00:00:22:00
 what happens if you take all those people and combine them into a single collaborative body

6
00:00:23:06 --> 00:00:27:00
 and then publish under a nom de plume for the collective, 

7
00:00:27:14 --> 00:00:29:13
for example, William Shakespeare, 

8
00:00:30:18 --> 00:00:35:15
and have the public assume that it’s just another one of us?

