2
00:00:00:11 --> 00:00:03:09
For example, think of an art directorial body that’s 

3
00:00:03:12 --> 00:00:06:05
a hundred people crowdsourced on Amazon Turk 

4
00:00:06:25 --> 00:00:10:06
instead of the Grammy Award winning 

5
00:00:10:09 --> 00:00:13:29
dude who sits at a desk in an advertising firm. 

6
00:00:14:26 --> 00:00:16:08
Which one could be stronger? 

7
00:00:17:25 --> 00:00:19:16
 I’d like to find out, you know?

