2
00:00:01:01 --> 00:00:05:11
I'm trying to create a glucose metabolism rate high

3
00:00:05:19 --> 00:00:07:25
 which is something you get when you play Tetris 

4
00:00:08:13 --> 00:00:13:09
and you see the little boxes and then you walk away and you still see the boxes.  

5
00:00:13:12 --> 00:00:17:11
You go out into the world and you say, hey, look at that trashcan over there?

6
00:00:17:14 --> 00:00:20:17
  Oh, wait, it’s a Tetris shape, cause look it’s an L somehow.

