2
00:00:00:29 --> 00:00:03:26
I got a TI-82 calculator when I took geometry

3
00:00:03:29 --> 00:00:06:16
 in high school and that was the mid 90s. 

4
00:00:06:19 --> 00:00:09:12
Shortly after, we got a Windows 95 box, 

5
00:00:09:15 --> 00:00:12:23
and I think it was just a continuation of our

6
00:00:13:28 --> 00:00:17:16
Tiger Handheld LCD videogames to a Nintendo

7
00:00:17:20 --> 00:00:21:14
  entertainment system, to Sega Genesis, it was just kind of, 

8
00:00:21:17 --> 00:00:26:01
 okay, I see that the Nintendo is more than just entertainment, said my father. 

9
00:00:26:04 --> 00:00:28:22
It’s doing more for you and you are learning, 

10
00:00:28:25 --> 00:00:33:23
so let’s step up a notch, and we got America Online, and at that point I got in trouble.



