2
00:00:01:00 --> 00:00:04:07
You could say that they come from like different communities.

3
00:00:04:10 --> 00:00:07:28
There is the Processing community, Open Frameworks, Cinder.  There is 

4
00:00:08:02 --> 00:00:12:16
sort of the more data viz-y type folks, 

the people who are

5
00:00:12:24 --> 00:00:15:29
doing more sort of experimental tech hacks, 

6
00:00:16:22 --> 00:00:22:25
maybe more interactive installation, exhibition design,

7
00:00:23:23 --> 00:00:26:17
all sorts of different approaches.

8
00:00:26:21 --> 00:00:31:06
 I think what unites them is

9
00:00:33:09 --> 00:00:36:02
a sort of researcher-like mentality

10
00:00:36:05 --> 00:00:41:22
where they are really sort of on the frontiers

11
00:00:43:02 --> 00:00:45:17
of creatively engaging with technology

12
00:00:46:06 --> 00:00:50:15
and probing what is possible,

13
00:00:51:07 --> 00:00:53:08
what this technology means, 

14
00:00:53:11 --> 00:00:58:15
how it might be implemented in a

creative, cultural capacity.

