2
00:00:00:00 --> 00:00:05:18
Yeah, I think it’s a lot of people’s sort of personal stories about

3
00:00:05:21 --> 00:00:10:12
how they came to be doing what they are doing and what

4
00:00:10:15 --> 00:00:15:02
technology sort of drew them into this world,

5
00:00:15:05 --> 00:00:17:06
what

6
00:00:17:24 --> 00:00:22:06
what sort of capabilities it revealed to them

and how it empowered them

because I think ultimately that’s what it does for a lot of these people.

7
00:00:22:09 --> 00:00:26:10
and how it empowered them

because I think ultimately that’s what it does for a lot of these people.

