2
00:00:01:09 --> 00:00:05:13
It’s not about visual representation, it’s not about descriptive representation,

3
00:00:05:20 --> 00:00:08:08
 like it would be in writing or in imagery. 

4
00:00:08:14 --> 00:00:12:05
It’s about representation that is dynamic and

5
00:00:13:01 --> 00:00:18:06
  represents the system of the elements and the relationships between those 

6
00:00:20:06 --> 00:00:22:24
and then the metaphor sort of

7
00:00:24:22 --> 00:00:30:04
 is embedded in that, in how those elements relate to each other.

