2
00:00:01:09 --> 00:00:04:24
Well, okay, so it’s hard not to see it as a journey,

3
00:00:04:27 --> 00:00:09:19
 because it is represented as a journey, but 

4
00:00:09:22 --> 00:00:13:13
I think for me it’s something where there is a movement forward which is 

5
00:00:13:16 --> 00:00:15:25
important, and then there

6
00:00:17:20 --> 00:00:20:28
is kind of there is the prescribed idealized 

7
00:00:21:01 --> 00:00:24:23
 thing and then there is how the world pushes back on that thing 

8
00:00:26:12 --> 00:00:28:17
and the reality

9
00:00:28:20 --> 00:00:32:18
that’s created from the interaction of the two.

