2
00:00:00:00 --> 00:00:04:27
I was so excited basically when I started computing, I started on East German hardware, 

3
00:00:05:00 --> 00:00:07:09
and we had absolutely nothing.  

4
00:00:07:12 --> 00:00:10:21
Those machines they cost like the equivalent of three months of income 

5
00:00:10:24 --> 00:00:15:04
and they came with literally nothing, just a manual how to assemble it and 

6
00:00:15:07 --> 00:00:16:08
that was it.

