2
00:00:01:00 --> 00:00:05:27
And it’s not that I want everyone to be a machine.  It’s absolutely not like that, 

3
00:00:06:11 --> 00:00:10:15
but I think there’s so much to be learned about our own nature.

4
00:00:10:18 --> 00:00:14:29
 I think most of the time when I am programming, I spend more time thinking about 

5
00:00:15:02 --> 00:00:17:06
how to structure something, 

6
00:00:17:09 --> 00:00:19:05
how it should be named, 

7
00:00:19:08 --> 00:00:22:29
what are the kinds of things, how they should fit together.

8
00:00:23:06 --> 00:00:25:03
rather than actually writing code.

