2
00:00:00:28 --> 00:00:05:00
…He is basically explaining how the database works, 

3
00:00:05:03 --> 00:00:07:18
and he says that that’s one point here

4
00:00:07:21 --> 00:00:11:16
 and then you go around and then there’s another audio sample there and another one there 

5
00:00:11:19 --> 00:00:14:20
and because this is closer, this is the one which is matched, 

6
00:00:15:26 --> 00:00:17:29
and he explains everything like that.

