2
00:00:01:15 --> 00:00:04:05
…Tera or petabytes of data, 

3
00:00:04:10 --> 00:00:07:14
it’s so irrelevant, because what really matters is 

4
00:00:07:17 --> 00:00:10:18
what is the information content in that data, 

5
00:00:10:21 --> 00:00:13:15
you know? Data on its own is just noise.  

6
00:00:13:18 --> 00:00:16:26
If no one processes that data, it’s meaningless.  

7
00:00:16:29 --> 00:00:17:26
It's

8
00:00:18:04 --> 00:00:19:25
really just dust.

