2
00:00:00:11 --> 00:00:06:04
Because it’s really you can see the visual feedback. You can actually get immediate results, 

3
00:00:06:07 --> 00:00:11:09
which are interesting to our eyes and interesting to people who are absolutely new to this field,

4
00:00:11:12 --> 00:00:16:23
and I think this is also one of the reasons why, for instance, Processing really became that popular, 

5
00:00:16:26 --> 00:00:21:03
 because it gives you that semi-immediate feedback, you know?

6
00:00:21:06 --> 00:00:24:03
 By now, there are already much better tools which give you 

7
00:00:24:06 --> 00:00:29:20
really immediate feedback.  You type one line of code, you press enter, and there’s your result.

