2
00:00:00:00 --> 00:00:00:27
That was it. 

3
00:00:01:00 --> 00:00:04:03
So we had like an afternoon course in school 

4
00:00:04:06 --> 00:00:05:23
 when I was 13, 

5
00:00:05:26 --> 00:00:09:06
and the task was basically to write our own game, 

6
00:00:09:09 --> 00:00:14:04
and we had the whole school year time and we did it as a group,

7
00:00:14:07 --> 00:00:19:09
 and this was I think the best school I ever had.  It was the hardest school I ever had.

8
00:00:19:14 --> 00:00:23:29
 We were having one computer, I had 1 hour of computer time a week. 

9
00:00:24:02 --> 00:00:26:26
 Everything else had to happen with pencil and paper.  

10
00:00:26:29 --> 00:00:31:10
We had the instruction table of all the CPU commands and you basically 

11
00:00:31:13 --> 00:00:36:23
had to as a 13-year-old break down something you didn’t even understand in practice

12
00:00:37:07 --> 00:00:40:28
and had to in a way encode it as numbers and then have

13
00:00:41:01 --> 00:00:44:26
 that 1 hour to hack it all in and if you had one typo, that was it,

14
00:00:44:29 --> 00:00:46:09
 that week was gone

