2
00:00:01:02 --> 00:00:04:28
We have people who write demos in 256 bytes. 

3
00:00:05:01 --> 00:00:07:18
 These are 256 numbers 

4
00:00:07:21 --> 00:00:11:08
strung together to create an image or an animation, 

5
00:00:11:12 --> 00:00:15:10
and this is incredible, because the way actually you can only achieve this is by

6
00:00:15:13 --> 00:00:19:06
 knowing every single bit about the technology underneath,

7
00:00:19:09 --> 00:00:24:02
 knowing what command to use in which position so you can actually reuse 

8
00:00:24:05 --> 00:00:25:28
the code as data 

9
00:00:26:10 --> 00:00:27:26
to create something else, 

10
00:00:27:29 --> 00:00:32:15
and it’s incredibly cryptic, but it shows incredible mental strength 

11
00:00:32:18 --> 00:00:35:13
and intelligence to actually achieve something like that.

