2
00:00:00:27 --> 00:00:03:27
I really believe this is more of the future in terms of

3
00:00:04:02 --> 00:00:07:18
 being prepared for multicore architectures and 

4
00:00:07:21 --> 00:00:12:16
cloud computing and all of that stuff where it really matters to be able to parallelize

5
00:00:12:25 --> 00:00:16:02
 your process onto a number of machines or processors.

