2
00:00:00:07 --> 00:00:03:11
And actually programming for me is always about, 

3
00:00:03:16 --> 00:00:06:16
more than it is talking to a machine, it is about 

4
00:00:06:25 --> 00:00:10:23
figuring out how to break down a complex concept or system 

5
00:00:10:26 --> 00:00:15:09
into such small components that it can actually be explained to a machine,

6
00:00:15:13 --> 00:00:18:12
 and this is purely an analytical skill 

7
00:00:18:15 --> 00:00:21:04
and analytics can be applied to anything.

