2
00:00:01:06 --> 00:00:03:02
I didn’t really think

3
00:00:03:17 --> 00:00:08:00
 that hard about systems 

4
00:00:08:29 --> 00:00:12:01
and the kind of algorithmic approach to 

5
00:00:13:12 --> 00:00:18:19
experience, to just fundamental human experience, until I started working with game designers every day 

6
00:00:18:27 --> 00:00:21:29
at Area Code, so that’s stretching back maybe

7
00:00:22:09 --> 00:00:23:25
 8 or 9 years now,

8
00:00:24:04 --> 00:00:28:23
 and it was really sort of spending time with game designers

9
00:00:28:26 --> 00:00:33:13
who unlike most other people in the world

10
00:00:33:16 --> 00:00:36:05
 are actually creating a living system 

11
00:00:36:08 --> 00:00:39:10
that then people are going to engage

12
00:00:39:13 --> 00:00:44:18
 for hours of the day or thousands of hours over a lifetime 

13
00:00:44:21 --> 00:00:49:01
 and understanding that the essence of what they are doing 

14
00:00:49:04 --> 00:00:51:26
when they design something is designing 

15
00:00:51:29 --> 00:00:55:22
the boundaries and the constraints on a human experience, 

16
00:00:55:25 --> 00:01:00:02
and I think that spending a lot of time with 

17
00:01:00:05 --> 00:01:03:13
some of the most talented game designers around for a couple of years 

18
00:01:03:19 --> 00:01:08:13
sensitized me to the idea that that is a

19
00:01:08:16 --> 00:01:13:03
subset of a much broader activity that’s happening in the world

20
 --> 


