2
00:00:01:10 --> 00:00:05:06
There is a way to understand Sol LeWitt wall drawings 

3
00:00:05:09 --> 00:00:09:16
as passing an algorithmic, right, like you know

4
00:00:09:19 --> 00:00:13:20
it’s mundane to talk about it like that, but that’s effectively what’s happening 

5
00:00:13:23 --> 00:00:16:25
and what 

6
00:00:17:10 --> 00:00:22:07
 sort of forward thinking artists and curators 40 years ago 

7
00:00:22:13 --> 00:00:25:28
were sort of foreseeing and what has really come true is that 

8
00:00:26:01 --> 00:00:30:02
(What) the shift that will happen will be the shift from artists making 

9
00:00:30:05 --> 00:00:33:15
things that reflect their vision

10
00:00:33:18 --> 00:00:37:01
 of the world, which is what artists do for a living,

11
00:00:37:05 --> 00:00:41:21
to actually making tools that allow other people to see as they see.

