2
00:00:00:17 --> 00:00:03:20
That underneath it is the idea that 

3
00:00:04:26 --> 00:00:08:07
there is a world that you can engage.

4
00:00:09:09 --> 00:00:12:01
that has no consequences.

