2
00:00:00:29 --> 00:00:04:02
At least for me it’s always been useful when working 

3
00:00:04:05 --> 00:00:07:01
to know exactly what it is you don’t want to do. 

4
00:00:07:04 --> 00:00:12:06
 Sometimes when you are trying to figure out what to do, it’s helpful to figure out what you so specifically don’t want to do

5
00:00:12:09 --> 00:00:15:17
and in that moment, the thing that we so specifically did not want to do

6
00:00:15:20 --> 00:00:17:06
 was called Second Life, 

7
00:00:17:09 --> 00:00:20:19
right.  That was sort of the opposite of everything 

8
00:00:20:22 --> 00:00:25:04
 that we cared about and could imagine as meaningful

9
00:00:25:07 --> 00:00:28:06
 and what it was about Second Life is it said 

10
00:00:29:03 --> 00:00:31:07
the way that we will simulate 

11
00:00:32:24 --> 00:00:35:22
a set of experiences that you have never had before 

12
00:00:35:25 --> 00:00:41:24
will be through the mimetic

 reproduction of the world for your eye, 

13
00:00:42:07 --> 00:00:45:13
and that is such narrow bandwidth.  

14
00:00:45:16 --> 00:00:48:24
(Right,) It’s such a narrow idea 

15
00:00:48:27 --> 00:00:51:27
of how reality is formed in the human mind, 

16
00:00:52:13 --> 00:00:56:14
and what we were interested in was, well, how else

17
00:00:57:09 --> 00:00:59:10
 is reality formed in a way?

