2
00:00:00:05 --> 00:00:04:16
The primary mode of transmission 

3
00:00:04:19 --> 00:00:09:02
from the world into my machine 

4
00:00:09:05 --> 00:00:12:16
during my adolescent years was actually typing in 

5
00:00:12:19 --> 00:00:16:25
programs that were printed in magazines.  I have been thinking a lot about that recently

6
00:00:17:22 --> 00:00:21:01
how strange that is, right,

7
00:00:21:04 --> 00:00:25:19
 that basically so before there was a network to deliver it, 

8
00:00:26:12 --> 00:00:28:10
 we used paper to do that.  

9
00:00:28:13 --> 00:00:31:18
 We basically took a program, 

10
00:00:32:21 --> 00:00:37:07
printed it out, and then sent the printout to somebody to turn it back into a program…

