2
00:00:00:29 --> 00:00:05:04
So, I’ve really been thinking a lot about virtual space and 

3
00:00:05:07 --> 00:00:11:15
how we project ourselves and our identities into technological interfaces, 

4
00:00:11:18 --> 00:00:13:01
and I feel that 

5
00:00:13:25 --> 00:00:17:27
we do it in an extremely wide variety of ways currently.  

6
00:00:18:00 --> 00:00:21:25
So, there are things like video games which we all know and love 

7
00:00:21:28 --> 00:00:26:17
 and in a video game, you are using a physical interface to control an avatar 

8
00:00:26:20 --> 00:00:29:06
on a screen that comes to represent you,

9
00:00:29:09 --> 00:00:34:01
like this little person that you have that you are moving around through the space is you

10
00:00:34:12 --> 00:00:35:24
 and the fact that

11
00:00:36:04 --> 00:00:41:06
 people my age at least have grown up with this kind of relationship to digital space, 

12
00:00:41:09 --> 00:00:45:27
 it’s like we have been projecting ourselves into nonreal spaces since we were 

13
00:00:46:02 --> 00:00:48:18
(you know,) 7 years old, 

14
00:00:49:15 --> 00:00:52:25
and so we are so intimately familiar with this feeling of

15
00:00:53:07 --> 00:00:57:10
packaging your identity into a little virtual character

16
00:00:57:13 --> 00:01:00:12
 that I think we are only at the beginning

17
00:01:00:15 --> 00:01:02:26
of what’s going to happen with that kind of 

18
00:01:03:07 --> 00:01:05:10
 process and technology.

