2
00:00:00:04 --> 00:00:05:16
So, I think about if I see something like Casey Rees’ music visualizations where 

3
00:00:05:25 --> 00:00:07:13
it’s a generative program 

4
00:00:07:16 --> 00:00:12:06
that develops these really intricate colorful abstractions

5
00:00:12:09 --> 00:00:17:05
 both from a set of parameters that he developed and from the sound that’s being 

6
00:00:17:08 --> 00:00:19:21
played sometimes live by an orchestra, 

7
00:00:20:16 --> 00:00:24:13
I can describe how certain sounds develop certain 

8
00:00:24:16 --> 00:00:28:29
angular expressions on the canvas which happens to be a building maybe. 

9
00:00:29:02 --> 00:00:34:03
 I can describe how as the sound elevates where the volume becomes louder,

10
00:00:34:06 --> 00:00:39:11
the perspective shifts and the forms become more complex.

