2
00:00:01:02 --> 00:00:05:19
So the little digital world that exists in my mind 

3
00:00:06:06 --> 00:00:09:21
in my subconscious would be some combination of like

4
00:00:11:12 --> 00:00:15:28
 early videogames and like 8-bit spreads and 

5
00:00:16:06 --> 00:00:18:18
RGB colors. 

6
00:00:21:11 --> 00:00:22:11
That 

7
00:00:23:10 --> 00:00:27:19
style has always been really attractive to me or something, 

8
00:00:28:02 --> 00:00:33:07
so I guess the virtual space that I grew up with and that I would live in 

9
00:00:33:10 --> 00:00:38:25
is the language of videogames and polygons and pixels.

