2
00:00:01:02 --> 00:00:05:18
Sometimes new media artists underestimate the power that traditional art 

3
00:00:05:21 --> 00:00:09:13
can have and has had. I think as much as 

4
00:00:09:16 --> 00:00:13:26
a generative work or an interactive work can respond to its viewers, 

5
00:00:14:01 --> 00:00:17:26
a Rothko, for example, responds to its viewers as well. 

6
00:00:18:01 --> 00:00:20:19
 It’s so deep and so subtle 

7
00:00:20:22 --> 00:00:24:26
that the more time you spend with it, the more it gives back to you and

8
00:00:24:29 --> 00:00:28:12
 the different ways you look at it rewards you with different perspectives on

9
00:00:28:15 --> 00:00:31:13
  this thing that looks two dimensional and looks finite,

10
00:00:31:16 --> 00:00:33:05
but is actually a really 

11
00:00:34:08 --> 00:00:38:17
 complex and deep entity in itself.

