2
00:00:01:13 --> 00:00:04:23
It’s playful, it’s an experiment,

3
00:00:05:04 --> 00:00:08:08
 but I go into every piece even when there are kind of 

4
00:00:08:12 --> 00:00:10:05
crazy ideas thinking like, 

5
00:00:10:09 --> 00:00:14:22
if this seems good I am going to just keep going with it for the rest of my life.

