2
00:00:00:27 --> 00:00:05:20
Well, I think you are always constructing a version of yourself to present and

3
00:00:06:08 --> 00:00:09:07
(you know, there is the idea that)

4
00:00:10:02 --> 00:00:13:21
there is the idea of yourself that you have and there is the idea of 

5
00:00:13:24 --> 00:00:17:00
yourself that the other person has and your idea of them 

6
00:00:17:03 --> 00:00:20:25
and their idea of them and none of these things necessarily sync up

7
00:00:20:28 --> 00:00:24:14
 and when you are in physical space, maybe it’s a little bit easier,

8
00:00:25:02 --> 00:00:27:08
 there is more physical continuity,

9
00:00:28:12 --> 00:00:31:22
 and it’s harder to hide certain things or to only show 

10
00:00:31:25 --> 00:00:33:29
 the curated best stuff, 

11
00:00:34:02 --> 00:00:37:00
but I think in any case you are always kind of

12
00:00:37:09 --> 00:00:41:23
monitoring yourself and deciding how to portray yourself and I think 

13
00:00:42:04 --> 00:00:43:25
you do the same thing online.

