2
00:00:01:06 --> 00:00:04:23
I think my main goal is for the user to

3
00:00:05:04 --> 00:00:07:06
 have an experience where they 

4
00:00:08:01 --> 00:00:13:21
question their normal reality or they start to see things in a slightly different way 

5
00:00:13:27 --> 00:00:16:03
and for each person 

6
00:00:16:25 --> 00:00:20:22
that could be different, so I am not trying to create a really specific 

7
00:00:21:01 --> 00:00:23:07
experience, but I am trying to create

8
00:00:23:14 --> 00:00:26:17
sort of these provocations or these 

9
00:00:26:20 --> 00:00:31:16
 loopholes or ways of sort of bootstrapping ourselves out of our normal 

10
00:00:32:00 --> 00:00:33:17
way of seeing things.

