2
00:00:00:29 --> 00:00:04:08
Why do we use a keyboard, why do we use a mouse, 

3
00:00:04:11 --> 00:00:08:22
why is there a microphone attached to a computer?  It can take a video. 

4
00:00:09:22 --> 00:00:14:16
 What do you assume we do with them, what happens if you erase all the letters on the keyboard 

5
00:00:14:19 --> 00:00:16:21
becomes a tactile surface. 

6
00:00:17:05 --> 00:00:20:27
 What happens if you take the mouse and look at the optical sensor and 

7
00:00:21:00 --> 00:00:24:10
shine it different places and what is that device?  

8
00:00:24:27 --> 00:00:28:23
What is the microphone that you don’t use to record voice but to just pick of sounds? 

9
00:00:28:26 --> 00:00:32:09
 What is the video when it’s just about intensity seeking, searching, 

10
00:00:32:20 --> 00:00:36:16
what can you make with it?  Why can’t you make it as a rectangular screen

11
00:00:36:19 --> 00:00:40:08
and defy it, making polar coordinates, make it 3D. 

12
00:00:40:23 --> 00:00:42:08
 I was just playing around with that.

