2
00:00:00:00 --> 00:00:03:22
I was making things and I made this thing that responds to sound, 

3
00:00:03:29 --> 00:00:09:03
the reactive square, ten squares that respond to sound kind of an [Unclear] 

4
00:00:09:21 --> 00:00:13:25
and my kids make sounds like [Unclear] the square would change, and they would

5
00:00:13:28 --> 00:00:15:18
 laugh and be happy, and

6
00:00:15:25 --> 00:00:19:14
 one day we were at a computer store in Tokyo, 

7
00:00:19:20 --> 00:00:24:09
and of course, we walked up to the computer and we are making sounds like [Unclear] and

8
00:00:24:12 --> 00:00:28:19
 nothing is happening, of course.  The computer person says like what’s wrong with your kids, 

9
00:00:28:27 --> 00:00:32:14
and on realizing that maybe there is a way to make things and so

10
00:00:32:17 --> 00:00:34:27
 I make things for my kids to play with.



