2
00:00:00:00 --> 00:00:01:02
…still that 

3
00:00:01:16 --> 00:00:05:14
technology is made by people and there are assumptions built in.

4
00:00:05:28 --> 00:00:08:13
Code libraries are built by people.

5
00:00:08:20 --> 00:00:12:10
 Code limitations exist because library limitation exist.

6
00:00:12:16 --> 00:00:15:25
Why is it that making something in a Macintosh

7
00:00:15:28 --> 00:00:18:23
 graphically was easier than making in Windows, 

8
00:00:18:26 --> 00:00:22:19
because QuickDraw on the Mac was a superior API 

9
00:00:22:22 --> 00:00:25:13
by people who made a better API. 

10
00:00:25:22 --> 00:00:30:08
 So, I began to think how APIs really would limitation for expression. 

11
00:00:31:21 --> 00:00:35:12
 People think they are coding raw, but they are not. 

12
00:00:35:21 --> 00:00:38:19
They have libraries that support them.  

13
00:00:39:16 --> 00:00:42:21
Where is the control point began to become a question?

