2
00:00:00:00 --> 00:00:02:12
But different, it’s got to be human. 

3
00:00:02:15 --> 00:00:07:00
 These aren’t like max headroom type people.  They are [Unclear] people. 

4
00:00:07:08 --> 00:00:10:25
 They are being digitized in 2.5 day like this. 

5
00:00:11:00 --> 00:00:14:23
 It’s a piece people can talk about and remember,

6
00:00:14:26 --> 00:00:20:10
and as soon as you are done and you open source it, [Unclear] we can start doing it and playing with it…

