2
00:00:01:17 --> 00:00:04:22
I am a big believer in education 

3
00:00:05:14 --> 00:00:07:04
and mentorship. 

4
00:00:07:11 --> 00:00:10:14
 I had the chance of seeing some of the

5
00:00:11:19 --> 00:00:15:06
 great design people as my mentors 

6
00:00:15:22 --> 00:00:20:07
who before dying sort of passed the baton to me and 

7
00:00:20:10 --> 00:00:23:01
I want to hold true to that.  Example is…

