2
00:00:00:00 --> 00:00:05:02
And so I was spending every night running a system in Python.  

3
00:00:06:09 --> 00:00:10:05
I just wanted to learn things.  I always found myself like 4 years behind my grad students,

4
00:00:10:08 --> 00:00:13:25
so I thought I would catch up and it sounds like in a system and

5
00:00:14:04 --> 00:00:18:14
 I wanted to make a system that wasn’t just about computation,

6
00:00:19:02 --> 00:00:23:16
 it was more about hand gestures 

7
00:00:23:19 --> 00:00:27:17
 like drawings, and so I made a system that would encode my drawings 

8
00:00:27:20 --> 00:00:31:14
and gestures and colors that I like and it’s important to [Unclear] 

9
00:00:32:03 --> 00:00:35:19
and worked with that.  Those series of 

10
00:00:35:22 --> 00:00:40:06
pieces, there are seven of them, they are not on the webs.  You can’t see them actually. 

11
00:00:42:08 --> 00:00:45:29
Those things were all examples of a different technique I developed 

12
00:00:46:02 --> 00:00:48:29
to make more human view 

13
00:00:49:02 --> 00:00:52:00
 of what computation looks like and feels like and…

