2
00:00:02:08 --> 00:00:05:13
I am just glad to be alive everyday

3
00:00:05:16 --> 00:00:09:02
 and I am curious about that fact, and what I get to imagine 

4
00:00:09:08 --> 00:00:12:03
by being alive. that’s my driving force.

