2
00:00:01:07 --> 00:00:06:04
I think now we feel that we have kind of explored that area for a bit

3
00:00:06:07 --> 00:00:12:05
 I am interested in how to tell stories again 

4
00:00:12:29 --> 00:00:17:28
with that. This whole computation design

approach in world

5
00:00:18:04 --> 00:00:22:28
tends to look at natural phenomenon and tends to be a little bit ambient or abstract

6
00:00:24:01 --> 00:00:27:04
 currently we are really interested in how can we take that

7
00:00:27:08 --> 00:00:32:05
and use it to tell stories with people and create films again.

