2
00:00:00:29 --> 00:00:06:13
We tried to put our stuff out there, but I am aware it takes a lots of time and effort.

3
00:00:06:16 --> 00:00:11:16
 I am really thankful for Karsten Schmidt, for example, 

4
00:00:11:19 --> 00:00:14:10
who has the ToxicLibs libraries.

5
00:00:14:14 --> 00:00:17:26
 I haven’t used them personally, but I have looked them

6
00:00:18:02 --> 00:00:21:29
through many times and always learned new tricks how to do things, 

7
00:00:22:02 --> 00:00:23:09
and they're good references.

8
00:00:24:10 --> 00:00:28:02
I think we were talking yesterday about Paul Burke

9
00:00:28:05 --> 00:00:32:15
who is kind of a shared

guru, basically.

10
00:00:33:07 --> 00:00:35:25
And it’s basically always the same people,

11
00:00:35:29 --> 00:00:38:26
 it comes to the same guys in the 80s,

12
00:00:39:00 --> 00:00:42:13
Paul Burk, Craig Reynolds, Carl Sims,

13
00:00:42:18 --> 00:00:47:19
they are sort of same the equivalent to (professional skateboarder) Rodney Mullen in the creative coding world.

14
00:00:48:14 --> 00:00:52:08
They have all contributed something that I am still 

15
00:00:52:25 --> 00:00:55:04
 trying to mimic or trying to learn from

