2
00:00:01:04 --> 00:00:04:15
I think there are two ways to explore it, there’s for one: 

3
00:00:05:16 --> 00:00:06:16
I really

4
00:00:07:02 --> 00:00:11:22
that kind of relates back to let’s say my early education in creative coding which was

5
00:00:11:27 --> 00:00:16:07
which was in Processing alpha,

beta days and

6
00:00:16:19 --> 00:00:19:04
 that kind of time when I looked up to

7
00:00:19:07 --> 00:00:22:15
the big guys and learned lots of tricks

8
00:00:22:19 --> 00:00:25:09
by looking through their code and there

9
00:00:25:12 --> 00:00:27:05
also there was this whole

10
00:00:27:08 --> 00:00:30:14
really vibrant vibe online,

11
00:00:31:10 --> 00:00:35:08
 lots of guys showing little new snippets

12
00:00:35:11 --> 00:00:40:09
 and I think that was an interesting time basically for several years

13
00:00:40:12 --> 00:00:44:29
until I think there was a certain point of satisfaction reached

14
00:00:45:02 --> 00:00:48:21
where everyone has kind of tried out everything and

15
00:00:48:24 --> 00:00:51:15
at least the obvious areas

16
00:00:51:18 --> 00:00:56:08
and then moved on to apply to bigger projects.

