2
00:00:01:01 --> 00:00:03:20
The link to music is quite important, and I think

3
00:00:03:23 --> 00:00:05:07
code is

4
00:00:05:11 --> 00:00:10:01
in a way a great language to speak

code is in a way a great language to speak

speak to both areas in a way.

5
00:00:10:04 --> 00:00:11:03
So

6
00:00:11:06 --> 00:00:15:01
I was always interested in the visual side, I was always interested in the audio side, and

7
00:00:15:04 --> 00:00:18:26
code is kind of a tool where we can talk to both.

8
00:00:19:00 --> 00:00:22:11
You’re not necessarily a master painter or a master sound, 

9
00:00:22:28 --> 00:00:27:07
guy, so it leads to collaboration naturally, 

10
00:00:28:21 --> 00:00:30:24
and it’s a great glue in a way,

11
00:00:30:27 --> 00:00:34:12
great practical glue to bring the pieces together 

12
00:00:34:15 --> 00:00:37:19
and also add something new

this whole

13
00:00:37:24 --> 00:00:40:27
way of composing stuff, in real-time,

14
00:00:41:00 --> 00:00:43:29
I mean, that’s another big topic for what we do.

