2
00:00:00:29 --> 00:00:03:17
you are sculpting possibility space

3
00:00:03:21 --> 00:00:07:28
which sounds big, but in a way that’s what it is is

4
00:00:08:00 --> 00:00:09:08
you are adding 

5
00:00:09:22 --> 00:00:13:10
with those little lego bricks of code and language that you have,

6
00:00:13:13 --> 00:00:17:11
you put them together and you add more possibilities

7
00:00:17:14 --> 00:00:21:05
with every new brick, basically your possibilities increase 

8
00:00:21:28 --> 00:00:23:16
many times and that’s

9
00:00:24:05 --> 00:00:29:00
 in a way this adding and taking away that’s kind of the design process now.

10
00:00:29:03 --> 00:00:33:10
it's

I still feel in control, but I like to be surprised.

11
00:00:33:13 --> 00:00:35:04
I think that’s the beauty of it, 

12
00:00:35:29 --> 00:00:38:21
the thing when a system goes beyond

13
00:00:38:24 --> 00:00:41:28
what you naturally understand it to do

14
00:00:42:01 --> 00:00:44:11
sometimes you have something that surprises you 

15
00:00:45:07 --> 00:00:48:03
and I always look for that, that one moment basically.



