2
00:00:01:00 --> 00:00:04:16
There is a nice quote by Will Wright who is

3
00:00:04:19 --> 00:00:08:29
the inventor SimCity and the Sims and other games,

4
00:00:09:02 --> 00:00:13:07
 I highly respect, and he said basically as a

5
00:00:13:22 --> 00:00:18:01
game designer, but I think the same applies to creative coding and these kinds of arts,

6
00:00:18:04 --> 00:00:21:07
 you are sculpting possibility space,

7
00:00:21:11 --> 00:00:25:17
which sounds big, but in a way that’s what it is. 

8
00:00:25:20 --> 00:00:27:00
You are adding

9
00:00:27:12 --> 00:00:31:00
with those little lego bricks of code and language that you have, 

10
00:00:31:03 --> 00:00:35:00
you put them together and you add more possibilities and

11
00:00:35:03 --> 00:00:38:27
with every new brick basically your possibilities increase

12
00:00:39:00 --> 00:00:41:05
many times. and that's

13
00:00:41:24 --> 00:00:46:19
 in a way this adding and taking away that’s kind of the design process now.

14
00:00:46:23 --> 00:00:50:29
it's

I still feel in control, but I like to be surprised.

15
00:00:51:02 --> 00:00:52:23
I think that’s the beauty of it, 

16
00:00:53:22 --> 00:00:56:10
the thing when a system goes beyond

17
00:00:56:14 --> 00:00:58:22
what you naturally understand it to do

18
00:00:58:24 --> 00:01:02:05
and sometimes have something that surprises you.

19
00:01:03:01 --> 00:01:05:25
and I always look for that, that one moment basically.

