2
00:00:00:07 --> 00:00:03:13
Well, okay, the way that I really see it is that,

3
00:00:03:27 --> 00:00:09:02
yes, I am approaching a potentially infinite space of possible outcomes,

4
00:00:09:05 --> 00:00:14:13
 but I am also shaping that possible space,

5
00:00:14:16 --> 00:00:17:25
I mean, just by existing human constrained randomness,

6
00:00:17:28 --> 00:00:21:28
so the idea of like authorless generative works, I don’t believe in that all,

7
00:00:22:01 --> 00:00:27:07
because the work does not exists apart from its creation by the author. 

8
00:00:27:10 --> 00:00:32:02
That said you can put into it ways of sort of 

9
00:00:32:09 --> 00:00:34:01
co-discovering with machines, 

10
00:00:34:04 --> 00:00:38:26
that’s actually something I am fond of talking about like co-discovery with the algorithmic, 

11
00:00:38:29 --> 00:00:42:28
like actually figuring out things that you might not have found out on your own,

12
00:00:43:01 --> 00:00:48:03
but it doesn’t mean that the algorithm gains agency or that it’s creating itself, because it isn’t,

13
00:00:48:06 --> 00:00:53:25
I mean, unless you are doing something extremely esoteric, the algorithm is defined quite tightly by the author.

