2
00:00:01:00 --> 00:00:05:09
Early on in a piece, I leave the parameters kind of wide open,

3
00:00:05:12 --> 00:00:10:08
so that I get results that are kind of wildly out of the playing field

4
00:00:10:11 --> 00:00:12:06
and then I narrow it down after.

