2
00:00:01:02 --> 00:00:05:16
A lot of my work is influenced by the electronic music scene and even the rave scene

3
00:00:05:19 --> 00:00:09:25
where music was a physical and sensory experience,

4
00:00:09:28 --> 00:00:12:14
where you did not isolate between

5
00:00:12:17 --> 00:00:18:04
the sensory experience of being in that space and sort of intellectual experience of listening to music.

6
00:00:18:07 --> 00:00:21:22
I see my works in that sense 

7
00:00:21:25 --> 00:00:25:18
that I would like to reach your cerebral cortex

8
00:00:25:21 --> 00:00:30:28
before you have the time to filter your perceptions through cultural conventions.

9
00:00:31:01 --> 00:00:34:15
Basically, I want to reach your brain by using really bold colors

10
00:00:34:18 --> 00:00:38:27
before you have the prejudice to say like oh, that’s some techno bullshit I don’t need to pay attention to.

