2
00:00:00:00 --> 00:00:03:24
Yeah, for me it’s very much a continuing process of exploration,

3
00:00:03:27 --> 00:00:07:16
of discovering one form or one structure 

4
00:00:07:19 --> 00:00:10:17
or an approach to a certain algorithm

5
00:00:10:20 --> 00:00:12:24
and then seeing where that takes me

6
00:00:12:27 --> 00:00:16:20
 and then the next time I wake up in the morning and think like I have to make a new piece, 

7
00:00:16:23 --> 00:00:20:09
 I might build on something that exists already or I might take it somewhere else.

