2
00:00:01:02 --> 00:00:03:01
People sometimes ask me why do you what you do

3
00:00:03:04 --> 00:00:07:29
and actually the sort of real answer for me is because these things are in my head.

4
00:00:08:02 --> 00:00:13:20
I do these things because those are structures that I sort of somehow perceive.

5
00:00:13:23 --> 00:00:16:11
I mean, I am not claiming to be a synesthete or anything like that,

6
00:00:16:14 --> 00:00:21:25
but literally these are structures that I sort of find myself wondering about and then I explore them.

