2
00:00:00:00 --> 00:00:02:28
I actually think it’s a little dirtier than that.

3
00:00:03:01 --> 00:00:06:24
We are not sort of just wandering around in a pretty garden finding beautiful things.

4
00:00:06:27 --> 00:00:08:21
 It’s a little more complicated.

