2
00:00:00:00 --> 00:00:05:00
So, the metaphor of the artist as gardener does come up quite a bit in relationship to code,

3
00:00:05:03 --> 00:00:07:10
and it has some relevance. 

4
00:00:07:13 --> 00:00:09:26
 For me, I sometimes choose that approach.

5
00:00:09:29 --> 00:00:15:04
Sometimes I actually literally set up a system to generate a 100 random variations and I pick between them,

6
00:00:15:07 --> 00:00:18:08
other times it’s a much more sort of tightly controlled system.

7
00:00:18:11 --> 00:00:22:03
 I don’t typically like systems where I am controlling all the parameters,

8
00:00:22:06 --> 00:00:23:24
that’s not something I normally do.

9
00:00:23:27 --> 00:00:26:13
There might be situations in which there is something you want,

10
00:00:26:16 --> 00:00:30:06
but I prefer to find forms instead of sort of

11
00:00:30:09 --> 00:00:33:27
top-down designing them from scratch.

12
 --> 


