2
00:00:00:22 --> 00:00:04:09
It’s very hard though to get it right, and certainly

3
00:00:04:12 --> 00:00:08:04
if you are working at a company

4
00:00:08:07 --> 00:00:13:22
and want to create things that are actually useful to people, you want to be on the useful edge.

5
00:00:13:25 --> 00:00:18:19
I think for me actually one of the trickiest places to be often is the

6
00:00:18:22 --> 00:00:21:08
 useful and interesting, but not beautiful,

7
00:00:21:11 --> 00:00:25:16
and I have actually had a couple of experiences of creating tools internally

8
00:00:25:19 --> 00:00:30:27
for business needs that I feel like are not really that aesthetically pleasing. 

9
00:00:31:00 --> 00:00:37:02
You would never put them in a museum,  you never look at them and to say, oh, wow, that’s cool,

10
00:00:37:05 --> 00:00:43:04
but for the people who are using that data, it’s the best possible way to present the data,

11
00:00:43:07 --> 00:00:48:26
and that often is a little bit tricky if you are sort of a standard creative coder type

12
00:00:48:29 --> 00:00:54:18
because you really want the output of what you do to be gorgeous.  You want people to think it’s cool at some level.

13
00:00:55:10 --> 00:00:59:11
At the end of the day, it’s like if all people want is to get things done,

14
00:00:59:14 --> 00:01:04:07
there are times when you just want to make it useful and you have to kind of reign yourself in.

