2
00:00:01:08 --> 00:00:04:25
Words are extremely powerful. They are an important way of thinking,

3
00:00:04:28 --> 00:00:08:07
 and so by visualizing words, 

4
00:00:08:10 --> 00:00:11:18
we can start to visualize a whole realm of thought and a realm of knowledge

5
00:00:11:21 --> 00:00:16:17
 that would be impossible if we just stuck to pure images or numbers.

