2
00:00:00:17 --> 00:00:04:03
I love the idea that we are learning more and more about how the brain works,

3
00:00:04:06 --> 00:00:07:21
 and I would love to see better visualizations of 

4
00:00:07:24 --> 00:00:10:27
how I myself think.  I think that would be fascinating.

