2
00:00:00:00 --> 00:00:03:00
The difference is that if you just look at raw data,

3
00:00:03:03 --> 00:00:07:02
you often will see something mildly interesting you may have noted before. 

4
00:00:07:05 --> 00:00:11:09
If you look at a graph of inflation,

5
00:00:11:12 --> 00:00:15:17
you will see it’s going up over time and it’s kind of interesting. 

6
00:00:15:20 --> 00:00:21:10
We all know inflation is steady, so that the value of the dollar goes down over time. 

7
00:00:21:13 --> 00:00:23:20
 That itself is not so interesting.

