2
00:00:00:21 --> 00:00:05:00
Trying to see thought in any way is completely fascinating.

3
00:00:05:03 --> 00:00:08:13
I love looking at MRI scans, even though I don’t understand them,

4
00:00:08:16 --> 00:00:13:02
it’s the idea that you have access to something about how we are actually thinking,

5
00:00:13:05 --> 00:00:16:18
and with computers you actually do have access to certain things

6
00:00:16:21 --> 00:00:19:25
and with simple algorithms — there are beautiful visualizations 

7
00:00:19:28 --> 00:00:24:04
of sorting algorithms that can help you understand them.

8
00:00:24:07 --> 00:00:28:14
I did a visualization of chess where you can sort of see a computer thinking about chess

9
00:00:28:17 --> 00:00:33:20
and it gives you some idea of just how many moves it’s considering, which is very fun.

