2
00:00:00:26 --> 00:00:05:21
If you see something that is showing you something you didn’t know it was there

3
00:00:05:24 --> 00:00:09:00
 to begin with, you see complexity that wasn’t there.

4
00:00:09:03 --> 00:00:12:04
An example of this for me is

5
00:00:12:07 --> 00:00:15:16
when I created a map of the wind with Fernanda Viegas,

6
00:00:15:19 --> 00:00:19:26
and I had this image in my mind of wind

7
00:00:19:29 --> 00:00:21:28
just flowing from west to east basically,

8
00:00:22:01 --> 00:00:26:12
 and I was like it can’t be quite that simple, but I am sure that’s what happens ultimately, 

9
00:00:26:15 --> 00:00:30:03
and the first time that we actually created visualizations that let us see 

10
00:00:30:06 --> 00:00:33:15
the full flow of the wind for the US, I was shocked. 

11
00:00:33:18 --> 00:00:37:18
 I had no idea that it traveled in so many different directions and 

12
00:00:37:21 --> 00:00:40:25
similarly when we ended up doing a couple of 

13
00:00:40:28 --> 00:00:43:12
trial visualizations of wind across the world,

14
00:00:43:15 --> 00:00:48:21
that was also really interesting, because I realized oh, it goes west to east in some places, east to west in other places.

15
00:00:48:24 --> 00:00:54:14
I immediately remembered, oh, yeah, I learned all about navigation in the 1500s

16
00:00:54:17 --> 00:00:56:27
and how boats would use these winds

17
00:00:57:00 --> 00:01:01:13
 and suddenly everything came together for me, and I was like aha, I see it now, I get it,

18
00:01:01:16 --> 00:01:05:09
and that gave me a framework I think to help me understand

19
00:01:05:12 --> 00:01:09:08
how the wind works in general, and it helped me understand the details.

