2
00:00:00:29 --> 00:00:05:21
You have a subject that you want to explore, but you don’t know what the story is you want to tell. 

3
00:00:05:24 --> 00:00:10:18
The story that you want to tell unfolds as you explore the subject.

