2
00:00:01:03 --> 00:00:05:28
One thing right now that I’m really obsessed with is complexity from simplicity. 

3
00:00:07:24 --> 00:00:12:15
I think the whole world is based on this. Our very existence, evolution, 

4
00:00:12:29 --> 00:00:17:19
life itself is something which is incredibly complicated

5
00:00:17:23 --> 00:00:20:07
but it came from simplicity.

