2
00:00:01:07 --> 00:00:05:28
So what happens is, you get these pulses, and then those pulses are in sync, 

3
00:00:06:01 --> 00:00:10:12
and then they go out of sync, and then they come back into sync.

