2
00:00:01:02 --> 00:00:05:23
The engineering, that's never been an issue cos it's not "I don't wanna be an engineer." 

3
00:00:05:26 --> 00:00:12:05
The engineering facilitates to some degree. I use what I need to use of the engineering. 

4
00:00:12:08 --> 00:00:18:16
Not so much in the music but in what I do. It's just problem solving really.

