2
00:00:01:06 --> 00:00:06:15
Obviously, partners always hate computers, right?! So I have a big thing with my wife, where 

3
00:00:06:18 --> 00:00:08:29
‘you’re always on your computer! What are you doing, why are you always on your computer?!’ 

4
00:00:09:02 --> 00:00:15:02
And it’s like, it’s not a computer, it’s a window into this other universe, 

5
00:00:15:05 --> 00:00:18:06
where, in that other universe, I am God!   

