2
00:00:01:20 --> 00:00:07:00
What I like to do is create these imaginary universes, 

3
00:00:07:03 --> 00:00:10:07
and these imaginary universes share 

4
00:00:10:19 --> 00:00:16:03
one thread of connection with the real world, and everything else is imaginary.

