2
00:00:00:28 --> 00:00:04:16
It creates an unfamiliar familiarity, and I really like that. 

3
00:00:04:19 --> 00:00:09:22
You look at it and you notice ‘there’s something in there that I recognize but I don’t know what it is.’

