2
00:00:00:00 --> 00:00:05:24
So I say ‘OK, start moving,’ and ‘gather up, go around, create swirls,’ 

3
00:00:05:27 --> 00:00:13:06
you know, ‘start quivering,’ ‘I want to express fear, I want to express solitude, I want to express different emotions.’ So, 

4
00:00:13:09 --> 00:00:17:28
it’s a very abstract narrative, it’s a journey through different emotions. 

5
00:00:18:01 --> 00:00:22:18
You can’t really call it a film. It’s a bunch of lines, basically. 

