2
00:00:00:25 --> 00:00:06:21
At that point in time, I was hearing every single layer of the song, 

3
00:00:06:29 --> 00:00:11:11
spatialized, like the voice was ‘here,’ the drums were ‘here,’ 

4
00:00:11:14 --> 00:00:14:17
that was ‘there’. It had complete synesthesia anyway.

