2
00:00:01:10 --> 00:00:06:23
It’s again so representative of nature, it’s one of those things like fractals you 

3
00:00:06:26 --> 00:00:12:16
simulate in a computer and it is like ‘woah,’ endless things you can do with it.

