2
00:00:00:00 --> 00:00:06:29
In those days, you know, this was 1985 (in 1985 I was 10 years old), you have a computer and you want to play games. 

3
00:00:07:02 --> 00:00:12:23
To play a game you need to put a cassette in, fast-forward to the correct bit

4
00:00:12:26 --> 00:00:18:03
you’d put all the games on this cassette, and it would have a counter. 

5
00:00:18:06 --> 00:00:24:21
So you’d have to rewind, reset it to zero, and then look. ‘Oh, the game I want to play is Chuckie Egg. Chuckie Egg starts at 

6
00:00:24:24 --> 00:00:29:14
337, so fast-forward to 337…’ So you have to understand 

7
00:00:29:17 --> 00:00:35:13
what’s going on here. You have to understand that there’s data that’s on the magnetic tape, and you have to 

8
00:00:35:16 --> 00:00:41:01
fast-forward to the bit where the data for Chuckie Egg is. And then you have to… 

9
00:00:41:16 --> 00:00:47:23
I forget, you have to type, you have to press ‘play,’ and then you have to type ‘load,’ and then it would load. 

10
00:00:47:26 --> 00:00:53:16
So you have to understand! And while it was playing it would be [imitates machine noises] doing all the sounds. 

11
00:00:53:23 --> 00:00:59:22
So you get an understanding of this. And then also, you have to type ‘load,’ and then you run… 

12
00:00:59:25 --> 00:01:03:15
and so it was quite natural to ask ‘well, what else can I type?’

