2
00:00:01:10 --> 00:00:07:01
Actually, I’ll tell you who my real inspiration is, and I used to show this in my talks: 

3
00:00:07:04 --> 00:00:10:25
Tom and Jerry. As a four year old, I didn’t know about 

4
00:00:10:28 --> 00:00:15:18
Norman McLaren or Oskar Fischinger: all I knew was Tom and Jerry - 

5
00:00:15:21 --> 00:00:19:01
every movement [movement sounds]. 

6
00:00:19:04 --> 00:00:25:02
I used to show clips from Tom and Jerry. 

7
00:00:25:12 --> 00:00:32:17
One particular clip that I used to show was where they were ice-skating and every movement has this amazing score. 

8
00:00:32:29 --> 00:00:35:08
But the score is so well 

9
00:00:36:05 --> 00:00:42:05
composed to the movement that you don’t actually hear the music, it just becomes the sound of the movement. 

10
00:00:42:08 --> 00:00:47:14
That completely inspired me. Also obviously Fantasia. 

11
00:00:47:17 --> 00:00:51:07
What kid didn’t get blown away by Fantasia? 

