2
00:00:00:00 --> 00:00:06:07
It’s true, right?! As a programmer, you are God of this universe that this portal goes into. 

3
00:00:06:10 --> 00:00:08:29
So, erm, read into that what you will! 

4
00:00:09:12 --> 00:00:15:01
But, how is that not a creative outlet, right?! That’s the biggest creative outlet that there is.

