2
00:00:01:15 --> 00:00:06:24
When a project has arrived… that’s obviously a classic difficult one, isn’t it. 

3
00:00:06:27 --> 00:00:11:16
Do you mean, like, when I’m happy and it’s done? That’s usually a deadline.

