2
00:00:01:17 --> 00:00:05:17
"Mega Super Awesome". Actually MSA is my initials. 

3
00:00:05:20 --> 00:00:08:29
Mohammed Salem Akten is my full name. 

4
00:00:09:02 --> 00:00:15:23
And many many years ago when I was... trying to come up with a name for cos I registered a company. 

5
00:00:15:26 --> 00:00:20:14
It's just me... trying to come up with the name and it's hard to come up with a name.

6
00:00:20:29 --> 00:00:23:29
So I somehow 

7
00:00:24:08 --> 00:00:28:03
as all good ideas the idea came when I was sitting on the toilet, 

8
00:00:28:06 --> 00:00:34:13
and I thought "yeah, Mega Super Awesome Visuals Company. MSA is my initials, blur blur." 

9
00:00:34:19 --> 00:00:37:19
So MSA became my

10
00:00:38:04 --> 00:00:44:01
kind of thing, you know, like, my name space.

