2
00:00:00:00 --> 00:00:04:10
Yeah, I mean, I am really intrigued more by

3
00:00:05:01 --> 00:00:09:03
sort of the theoretical aspects,

4
00:00:09:25 --> 00:00:11:03
 and

5
00:00:13:07 --> 00:00:16:17
yeah, I don’t know I guess I don’t necessarily think about 

6
00:00:16:20 --> 00:00:19:17
the beauty dimension as much.

