2
00:00:00:09 --> 00:00:05:02
I guess usually a lot of the process is

3
00:00:05:23 --> 00:00:08:22
somewhat removing or

4
00:00:10:04 --> 00:00:14:11
 limiting the unexpected, so that we can 

5
00:00:16:05 --> 00:00:19:11
go about doing something that we intend.

