2
00:00:00:28 --> 00:00:03:02
We always wanted to have 

3
00:00:03:07 --> 00:00:06:17
some sort of direct collaboration, but usually it is now

4
00:00:06:20 --> 00:00:09:20
 that we get booked for VJ gigs and 

5
00:00:09:23 --> 00:00:12:10
we meet the musicians before 

6
00:00:12:13 --> 00:00:15:23
and then we just do something to the sound we hear.

