2
00:00:01:01 --> 00:00:02:15
In theory

3
00:00:02:18 --> 00:00:05:28
you could build the whole universe 

inside your computer, 

4
00:00:06:01 --> 00:00:11:22
you just don’t have enough power and then you will never get there and it would be boring to build the same thing all over again,

5
00:00:11:25 --> 00:00:13:15
 but in theory, you could. 

6
00:00:13:21 --> 00:00:16:16
 It’s something I find kind of stunning.

