2
00:00:00:26 --> 00:00:04:03
Your system will always be in a box like 

3
00:00:04:27 --> 00:00:08:10
pretty far away from the actual 

4
00:00:08:13 --> 00:00:10:24
reality we have outside just 

5
00:00:10:29 --> 00:00:15:06
because of its nature that it’s built on something entirely different, 

6
00:00:15:12 --> 00:00:17:23
just like bits and bytes.

