2
00:00:00:29 --> 00:00:04:14
With programming, you can do whatever you want,

3
00:00:04:23 --> 00:00:07:28
at some point, it’s 

4
00:00:08:23 --> 00:00:11:06
 I wouldn’t say biblical, but it’s like 

5
00:00:11:09 --> 00:00:15:25
there is nothing in the beginning or just as you have in history, it’s just an empty space 

6
00:00:15:28 --> 00:00:18:13
and then you can start throwing things in there…

