2
00:00:00:04 --> 00:00:05:10
And when I learned how that algorithm worked  in college, 

3
00:00:05:13 --> 00:00:10:28
it for me was a reflection on the  universe that we live in.  

4
00:00:11:17 --> 00:00:14:26
Given some initial  configuration and given a set of 

5
00:00:15:18 --> 00:00:18:09
four basic  rules, the rules of physics, 

6
00:00:19:04 --> 00:00:23:11
electromagnetism,  gravity, 

7
00:00:23:14 --> 00:00:26:11
the strong and weak nuclear forces,  

8
00:00:28:15 --> 00:00:33:19
given the simple set of rules and initial  configuration you have this impossibly complex  universe, 

9
00:00:34:00 --> 00:00:38:24
and Conway’s Game of Life was sort  of a reflection on that 

10
00:00:38:27 --> 00:00:43:08
incredibly elegant  structure, right, and like how you can get  profound complexity 

11
00:00:43:11 --> 00:00:46:26
not by starting with  complexity and just getting more complexity, 

12
00:00:46:29 --> 00:00:52:07
but by starting with something that can be  described in a paragraph and just emerging  from that.

