2
00:00:01:12 --> 00:00:05:07
How do I design something 

3
00:00:06:27 --> 00:00:11:08
that can be  described in a sentence that could be  understood at a glance, 

4
00:00:11:14 --> 00:00:15:08
but at the same time  is not limiting in its simplicity.

