2
00:00:01:06 --> 00:00:03:22
Edsger Dijkstra, the seminal computer  scientists 

3
00:00:03:25 --> 00:00:06:23
in his Turing acceptance lecture  

4
00:00:06:27 --> 00:00:09:14
said that programming has allowed human beings  

5
00:00:09:17 --> 00:00:12:14
to think thoughts previously unthinkable, 

6
00:00:12:26 --> 00:00:15:26
and  that’s the kind of thought that I think he  was referring to 

7
00:00:15:29 --> 00:00:20:21
is being able to see into  this impossibly deep iteration 

8
00:00:20:24 --> 00:00:26:15
and really  profoundly understand what it’s doing it, in  aggregate and at each iteration.

