2
00:00:01:00 --> 00:00:04:04
I always feel like when I develop like video  games, 

3
00:00:04:07 --> 00:00:06:03
whenever someone is playing one of my  video games, 

4
00:00:06:06 --> 00:00:10:00
that’s a little piece of  imagination that’s just springing to life and  just running.

