2
00:00:00:17 --> 00:00:04:20
I mean, the computer can do 4 billion  calculations a second at this point, 

3
00:00:04:28 --> 00:00:10:24
and what  that means is that you can write code 

that  specifies a loop for example 

4
00:00:10:27 --> 00:00:15:18
that will run a  100 million times doing different things on  each iteration, right, 

5
00:00:15:28 --> 00:00:19:17
and as a programmer you  can look at those three lines of code 

6
00:00:19:22 --> 00:00:22:24
and see  a 100 million iterations into the future 

7
00:00:22:27 --> 00:00:25:21
and  understand what that means in a single glance

