2
00:00:00:29 --> 00:00:03:24
What is the connection between the initial  state 

3
00:00:03:27 --> 00:00:07:15
and the rules and the kind of behavior  that you get, 

4
00:00:07:27 --> 00:00:10:00
and the answer is that there isn ’t one, right?  

5
00:00:10:03 --> 00:00:13:24
You can’t predict what it  will do without actually running through over  single step 

6
00:00:13:27 --> 00:00:16:19
and Conway’s Game of Life in that  way is strongly emerging.

