2
00:00:01:10 --> 00:00:03:08
Computation exists.  

3
00:00:03:11 --> 00:00:07:12
Computation is the  execution and the interpretation of rules 

4
00:00:07:15 --> 00:00:09:23
and  computers are just one way to do it.

