2
00:00:01:00 --> 00:00:03:22
Where math finds its place in Arab culture 

3
00:00:03:25 --> 00:00:06:05
is  these incredibly ornate 

4
00:00:07:04 --> 00:00:11:11
geometric designs that  decorate the insides and outsides of  buildings, 

5
00:00:11:14 --> 00:00:14:09
and when you read about how they  were made, 

6
00:00:14:27 --> 00:00:19:08
they were assembled by generally  skilled craftsmen, 

7
00:00:19:11 --> 00:00:23:01
but they were designed by  artists as algorithms.  

8
00:00:23:15 --> 00:00:25:23
So the instructions to  the craftsmen would be 

9
00:00:25:26 --> 00:00:29:05
place this black tile  then a red tile to the side 

10
00:00:29:08 --> 00:00:32:06
and then turn it  around, place a black tile here and then like  a long tile there 

11
00:00:32:09 --> 00:00:35:06
and it’s just instructions,  right, again instructive art form.

