2
00:00:00:00 --> 00:00:04:08
That’s certainly the most profound ,  certainly the most profound computer science  experience I ever had 

3
00:00:04:11 --> 00:00:08:29
and one of the most  profound life experiences that I ever had was  learning how that algorithm worked.  

4
00:00:10:16 --> 00:00:14:28
Conway’s  Game of Life is what’s called a zero player  game.

5
00:00:15:12 --> 00:00:18:26
The way it works is it divides the  universe into a grid, 

6
00:00:19:00 --> 00:00:23:15
a two-dimensional grid  of cells that are either filled or not filled  

7
00:00:23:29 --> 00:00:29:11
and as a player, you create an initial  configuration of cells that are filled and not  filled, 

8
00:00:29:23 --> 00:00:32:26
and then the algorithm runs over 

9
00:00:33:12 --> 00:00:36:27
that  the entire universe of cells 

10
00:00:37:07 --> 00:00:41:17
and implements a  set of very simple rules. 

11
00:00:42:13 --> 00:00:48:13
If an unfilled cell  has three filled cells around it, it becomes  filled.



12
00:00:48:27 --> 00:00:53:10
If a filled cell has more than three  filled cells around it, it becomes unfilled,  

13
00:00:54:05 --> 00:00:56:21
things like that, three rules like that. 

14
00:00:57:17 --> 00:01:03:18
Given  an initial configuration and those simple  rules, 

15
00:01:04:13 --> 00:01:09:04
the kind of profound complexity that  you can derive 

16
00:01:09:08 --> 00:01:12:07
is mind blowing.

