2
00:00:01:05 --> 00:00:06:03
That’s what it means I think conceptually to  me to express yourself through code is 

3
00:00:06:06 --> 00:00:11:07
to be  able to build a set of instructions to specify  a behavior that can 

4
00:00:11:10 --> 00:00:14:06
live and run independently  of any human being.

