2
00:00:00:00 --> 00:00:02:06
I am Ramsey Nasser.  I am a computer  scientists.

3
00:00:02:09 --> 00:00:05:26
My primary interest is in  programming language design 

4
00:00:05:29 --> 00:00:09:29
and code as a  medium of self-expression is how I have been  calling it.

