2
00:00:01:04 --> 00:00:04:03
So Minecraft is sort of the logical 

3
00:00:05:06 --> 00:00:09:12
world- building lego project.  

4
00:00:09:15 --> 00:00:13:27
Minecraft is a  fascinating study in 

5
00:00:14:13 --> 00:00:18:04
language design in an  abstract sense, 

6
00:00:18:07 --> 00:00:23:27
because the trick to language  design and 

the trick to the kind of flat...

7
00:00:26:01 --> 00:00:31:00
the trick to the kind of flat  relationship that I really envision is 

8
00:00:31:04 --> 00:00:35:00
if I am  making a tool and I am making a system, I am  obviously making 

9
00:00:35:03 --> 00:00:38:21
some set of primitives that  people are going to manipulate, right?  

10
00:00:39:27 --> 00:00:45:16
The  challenge is what is the minimal set of  primitives that I can create 

11
00:00:46:02 --> 00:00:49:13
that will allow  people and myself 

12
00:00:49:16 --> 00:00:54:03
to express the widest  variety of ideas.

