2
00:00:01:09 --> 00:00:04:23
The problem I have with virtual reality and with Second Life

3
00:00:04:26 --> 00:00:08:27
and stuff like that is that the aesthetics repels me,

4
00:00:09:00 --> 00:00:15:02
so you always feel this layer of artificiality

5
00:00:15:05 --> 00:00:20:12
which I never managed to reengage and feel comfortable there,

6
00:00:20:15 --> 00:00:25:28
so yeah, virtual version would be good,

7
00:00:26:01 --> 00:00:31:29
but the ones I’ve tested so far, I don’t think they can replace physicality.

8
00:00:32:02 --> 00:00:34:07
It doesn’t mean that physicality cannot be replaced,

9
00:00:34:10 --> 00:00:39:03
but what I have experienced so far, I wasn’t very impressed.

