2
00:00:01:01 --> 00:00:03:25
There is this almost full circle, 

3
00:00:03:28 --> 00:00:09:11
when you push something so far and everything is within the machine and within the computer,

4
00:00:09:14 --> 00:00:15:12
 there is naturally going to be a push to go back to where that started in the foundation of drawing…

