2
00:00:01:02 --> 00:00:03:23
Moving to Japan 

3
00:00:03:26 --> 00:00:08:08
and working under a camcorder, drawing on paper, which led me to working digitally and

4
00:00:08:11 --> 00:00:12:27
and then people would ask me to sign them and then I ended up drawing on people and then drawing on objects and 

5
00:00:13:00 --> 00:00:17:01
meeting someone at my show that got me interested in the US for the first time and

6
00:00:17:04 --> 00:00:19:04
 then moving to New York 

7
00:00:19:07 --> 00:00:23:23
and being a struggling artist again which challenged me to work in other mediums

8
00:00:23:26 --> 00:00:28:12
 and all these things are from luck, yeah, it’s from chance, but 

9
00:00:28:15 --> 00:00:33:12
those things only happen when you put stuff out, and people always say you are so lucky, 

10
00:00:33:16 --> 00:00:39:11
and I say why don’t you go out and create your own luck, create your own chance, because you can do that.

