2
00:00:01:05 --> 00:00:05:25
Someone saw this and they said, oh, can you do some live drawing at this event that we're putting on, 

3
00:00:05:29 --> 00:00:11:11
so I said, yeah, okay, but it’s quite small, so can I draw under a camcorder and project it, she was like, sure,

4
00:00:11:14 --> 00:00:15:29
 and I did it and I fell in love, because I just discovered that I was a performer, 

5
00:00:16:07 --> 00:00:20:20
I was a dancer, and I could create 

6
00:00:20:23 --> 00:00:25:01
the world that I was imagining in this very small world, I could 

7
00:00:25:17 --> 00:00:32:10
share and I could bring into reality and collaborate with the musicians and the sounds and we are all TV kids. 

8
00:00:32:14 --> 00:00:36:18
 If you see someone drawing here and a band is playing there, you don’t put them together,

9
00:00:36:21 --> 00:00:42:12
 but if you see projections or drawing happening on the screen with a band or with a DJ

10
00:00:42:15 --> 00:00:45:01
 you’re like, a-hah, the two are connected.

