2
00:00:01:07 --> 00:00:04:07
And it just happened to be that those bands were

3
00:00:04:10 --> 00:00:08:18
circuit-bending bands, they were noise bands, there were avant-garde bands, and

4
00:00:08:21 --> 00:00:13:25
 I drew to people that played static, shhhh for 45 minutes, 

5
00:00:13:28 --> 00:00:18:24
I drew to people that circuit bended machines, it was like

6
00:00:20:22 --> 00:00:24:00
and this was great, because I discovered that 

7
00:00:24:08 --> 00:00:28:09
I personally wouldn’t or couldn’t listen to this music, 

8
00:00:28:12 --> 00:00:34:19
but if you are performing to it, you have to switch off, you switch off your mind and you draw from your gut, 

9
00:00:34:23 --> 00:00:39:23
because if you are thinking about drawing to noise music or to static, nothing is going to happen,

10
00:00:39:26 --> 00:00:45:07
 but if you feel it and you really go there, you become a part of the music and you get to really create

11
00:00:45:10 --> 00:00:50:29
 a piece of work or drawing or performance which is really honest and it’s really in the moment,

12
00:00:51:02 --> 00:00:56:14
 and like I said, I fell in love with that straight away and it kind of continued from there.

