2
00:00:00:27 --> 00:00:06:06
It’s... basically performing with a computer system, is different stylistically, 

3
00:00:06:09 --> 00:00:11:01
so it might not be better or worse, but stylistically you get a different line, 

4
00:00:11:04 --> 00:00:15:14
and I am all about lines, drawing lines, drawing on walls, people 

5
00:00:15:17 --> 00:00:17:21
 doors, cars, shoes,

6
00:00:17:24 --> 00:00:23:03
 and working with computers and software you get a different quality of line, and I feel like that’s kind of special. 

7
00:00:23:06 --> 00:00:26:08
 It’s like an extension of your drawn analog lines.

8
00:00:26:11 --> 00:00:30:03
  It’s taking it into another dimension.

