2
00:00:00:01 --> 00:00:05:11
The great thing about traveling and meeting people is that

3
00:00:05:16 --> 00:00:09:10
 by yourself you might not think of these things, but when you are 

4
00:00:09:13 --> 00:00:14:06
put in a position or in a room with other creative people, you challenge each other, you come up with ideas,

5
00:00:14:09 --> 00:00:17:01
 and there’s lots of opportunities there.

