2
00:00:00:00 --> 00:00:03:14
I would find it very difficult to imagine 

3
00:00:03:17 --> 00:00:06:10
someone who creates lines through coding, because

4
00:00:06:13 --> 00:00:11:02
 it takes so much time and so much of your attention

5
00:00:11:05 --> 00:00:14:12
 in one space and in one moment and in one time. and it's...

6
00:00:14:17 --> 00:00:18:22
 It’s... It’s very solitary.  

7
00:00:18:25 --> 00:00:24:10
You have to sit there for like 8 hours, 9 hours, I don’t know how long people code for, but

8
00:00:24:13 --> 00:00:28:27
 I imagine it’s a long time and I find it very difficult to sit down for 5 minutes, 

9
00:00:29:00 --> 00:00:35:16
so I can’t imagine multiplying that by long time and actually physically working through this language.

10
00:00:35:19 --> 00:00:41:08
  I do imagine it would be extremely rewarding to 

11
00:00:41:16 --> 00:00:45:27
discover this new language and be able to code and write and make things happen, 

12
00:00:46:01 --> 00:00:51:14
but I do believe that in the future maybe coding will become more gestural. 

13
00:00:51:17 --> 00:00:57:25
Now it is you sit down and you do this and then there is a result and you do this and then there is a result. 

14
00:00:58:04 --> 00:01:01:07
 In the future, why isn’t coding more gestural?  

15
00:01:01:10 --> 00:01:06:26
Why can’t we use our body to create a code and therefore create a result or an effect, 

16
00:01:06:29 --> 00:01:09:25
and when that happens, I will happily be coding.

