2
00:00:01:00 --> 00:00:04:15
Working with someone like Zach is kind of special in the sense that

3
00:00:04:29 --> 00:00:10:14
 the way he thinks is coming from a completely different direction to what I am, 

4
00:00:10:17 --> 00:00:15:12
and the way we work together is using drawing and code, 

5
00:00:15:16 --> 00:00:21:04
I get to use my ideas which are from a more like physical drawn perspective

6
00:00:21:07 --> 00:00:27:04
 and Zach is coming from a perspective where it’s about the code and the language

7
00:00:27:07 --> 00:00:32:08
 and point A and point B and how you program that in between, 

8
00:00:32:12 --> 00:00:37:01
so the two do kind of meet, but from different directions 

9
00:00:37:04 --> 00:00:41:04
and I feel like meeting in the middle is really fun.

