2
00:00:00:00 --> 00:00:05:04
Thinking about the game Spore and the Sims and

 all these games that are sort of all these games that are sort of

3
00:00:05:07 --> 00:00:10:14
where these autonomous agents are living in a world and they operate with these simple rules and

4
00:00:10:17 --> 00:00:14:22
  just thinking about Starcraft and there is a lot of that types of elements, and interestingly enough

5
00:00:14:25 --> 00:00:21:00
 I wasn’t really thinking about games

 in making these examples or making the book, 

6
00:00:21:03 --> 00:00:24:22
but it is really my hope that some of these concepts could help people 

7
00:00:24:25 --> 00:00:28:22
in game programming for sure.

