2
00:00:00:00 --> 00:00:03:16
Once I started taking a course where it was like

 

3
00:00:03:19 --> 00:00:08:10
 hey you are going to learn, and　while you are learning to program, why don’t you draw some stuff on the screen, 

4
00:00:08:13 --> 00:00:15:02
that’s really where it kind of clicked that this was kind of

something where I could just sit and tweak the numbers forever and ever and ever

5
00:00:15:05 --> 00:00:17:23
  just to watch　slightly different things happen.

