2
00:00:00:00 --> 00:00:03:16
We live in this world, there are things like 

3
00:00:03:19 --> 00:00:08:17
gravity,there are things like plants and trees,

  there’s waves, there’s all sorts of stuffs.

4
00:00:08:20 --> 00:00:13:08
Anything that we see in the world around us, 

what would it mean to try to simulate that in code.

what would it mean to try to simulate that in code.  Whether that means

5
00:00:13:11 --> 00:00:19:20
 Whether that means, here is the actual mathematical formula and translate that 

 into code we can run in Processing,

6
00:00:19:23 --> 00:00:25:18
 or here is this tricky goofy openGL like blending effect that kind of looks like clouds.

