2
00:00:00:00 --> 00:00:04:24
For me, these days I spend more of my time teaching 

3
00:00:04:27 --> 00:00:07:17
than creating my own sort of things, so

4
00:00:07:21 --> 00:00:10:18
 to me the excitement is actually

5
00:00:11:26 --> 00:00:16:25
 is helping and teaching and allowing people to realize that

6
00:00:16:28 --> 00:00:21:12
 this thing called computer programming is a thing that they can do 

7
00:00:21:15 --> 00:00:26:27
and that they can enjoy doing and that they can do in a free, experimental goofy kind of way without

8
00:00:27:00 --> 00:00:32:19
this sort of like a pressure and exact science, sort of need for exactness.

