2
00:00:00:22 --> 00:00:04:07
On what level, if you can understand these simple tiny building blocks 

3
00:00:04:10 --> 00:00:08:10
and everything is just a nested system of these; 

4
00:00:08:17 --> 00:00:12:00
the body is a system of cells, 

5
00:00:12:03 --> 00:00:16:13
the city is a system of bodies, the world is a system of cities, you can go on and on and on,

6
00:00:16:15 --> 00:00:18:04
powers of 10 et cetera, 

7
00:00:18:07 --> 00:00:23:16
so that to me is a very exciting thing, this idea of

how far could we get 

8
00:00:24:08 --> 00:00:27:10
 in recreating our world through an algorithm.

