2
00:00:01:00 --> 00:00:06:28
There is an interesting Chuck Close quote I think which is that he considers computers to be a labor-saving device

3
00:00:07:01 --> 00:00:12:12
and that being a negative thing.  

I think on the one thing(hand)　this is something that computers offered. 

4
00:00:12:15 --> 00:00:18:07
  You can iterate and try certain ideas out very, very quickly 

that you could do.  

5
00:00:18:10 --> 00:00:20:24
On the other hand, there is a certain 

6
00:00:21:20 --> 00:00:26:18
quality to making something by hand, the slowness of that, 

7
00:00:26:24 --> 00:00:32:12
the sort of the methodology of the physicality of drawing that I think is also really special. 

8
00:00:32:15 --> 00:00:34:22
I don't know that there is neccessarily

9
00:00:35:29 --> 00:00:42:01
So, I don’t know that there are the things that a computer can do and things that a person can’t do.



