2
00:00:00:00 --> 00:00:03:18
When you first learn to program, and let’s say you are first learning in Processing, 

3
00:00:03:21 --> 00:00:08:22
you open up Processing and you learn here, I can draw a rectangle and I can draw a circle and I can draw a line

4
00:00:08:25 --> 00:00:12:01
 and I give them XY locations and I give them colors. 

5
00:00:12:04 --> 00:00:18:02
Okay, well, I want to do something more with that, but I have just started to learn, what's the next logical step? Well, make a lot of them,

what’s the next logical step?  Well, make a lot of them, 

6
00:00:18:05 --> 00:00:21:17
and I will just make them all random, all random positions, all random colors.

