2
00:00:01:02 --> 00:00:03:24
But I do like to think of it as telling a story

3
00:00:03:27 --> 00:00:08:05
,so there is this story which is 

what’s the beginning of the story,

4
00:00:08:08 --> 00:00:13:28
X equals X plus one where you have this thing you are drawing at the location X and you add one to it and it moves over here.

5
00:00:14:01 --> 00:00:19:03
You add one to it and it moves over here and that’s programming animation, that’s programming motion, the basic fundamentals, 

6
00:00:19:06 --> 00:00:24:04
 so you start there and then oh, you add Y, 

so now I have X and Y, I can make that into a vector,

7
00:00:24:07 --> 00:00:28:02
well that vector is it’s velocity, oh, that’s no longer constant.  

8
00:00:28:05 --> 00:00:31:11
 You could have an acceleration which the velocity changes, and now, 

9
00:00:31:14 --> 00:00:34:24
oh, but force equals mass times acceleration, okay, 

10
00:00:34:27 --> 00:00:39:24
 well, if I have acceleration, then there is this relationship between force and acceleration, so I can simulate forces.

then I can start to simulate forces, 

11
00:00:39:27 --> 00:00:42:10
so there is this like building up of concepts, 

12
00:00:42:13 --> 00:00:47:24
start with the very, very basic elements of the graphics and drawing and animation,

layer on this, layer on that, and then

13
00:00:47:27 --> 00:00:54:04
 just that and what’s sort of excitement about this is that basic motion, that just

14
00:00:54:07 --> 00:00:58:02
basic idea of motion, it’s there in every single example basically throughout the entire book,

15
00:00:58:05 --> 00:01:01:04
it’s just here is a fancier way to calculate the acceleration.

16
00:01:01:07 --> 00:01:05:23
Now we put a lot of those things together.  What if they interact with each other, what if we try to evolve them,

17
00:01:05:26 --> 00:01:09:26
 what if we try to recursively like structure them on top of each other,

18
00:01:09:29 --> 00:01:14:11
but thinking of that as a story that everything connects and

19
00:01:14:14 --> 00:01:17:27
 that you are sort of learning and building piece by pieces is kind of

20
00:01:18:00 --> 00:01:24:04
 whether that’s in reality actually in the book or just sort of a nice idea that I hopefully achieve, but that’s how I think about it.



