2
00:00:00:00 --> 00:00:03:00
I had done some programming when I was a kid.  

3
00:00:03:03 --> 00:00:06:02
I learned BASIC, I learned Assembly.  

4
00:00:06:05 --> 00:00:12:02
Even when I first moved to New York as an adult, I took an evening course in C programming and I thought 

5
00:00:12:05 --> 00:00:16:13
programming, maybe I would like that, I will take a course in that, 

6
00:00:16:16 --> 00:00:18:09
and I didn’t like it at all. 

