2
00:00:00:10 --> 00:00:05:04
I don’t know what this is like I think I'm seeing photons,

3
00:00:05:07 --> 00:00:07:21
but that’s just because it’s a very good theory.

4
00:00:08:13 --> 00:00:13:05
Maybe I am projecting like the Kinect like projecting my ideas out into the world and

5
00:00:13:08 --> 00:00:15:29
it’s bouncing back at me like we don’t really know,

6
00:00:16:02 --> 00:00:20:22
like we still haven’t figured out the cones and rods in our eyes and like do we really have to?

