2
00:00:00:13 --> 00:00:06:24
What I like and appreciate and why I like to work in this area is that there are 

3
00:00:06:27 --> 00:00:12:06
so many people who find new and different ways to 

4
00:00:12:09 --> 00:00:15:08
bring their ideas to life and to 

5
00:00:15:15 --> 00:00:18:24
create things that are beautiful, that are aesthetic, that are 

6
00:00:18:27 --> 00:00:22:22
interesting on a story level in a way, 

7
00:00:22:25 --> 00:00:28:20
and yeah, that’s a tribe that I like to be in, I guess.

