2
00:00:00:06 --> 00:00:03:29
That was often a really interesting back and forth 

3
00:00:04:02 --> 00:00:06:26
when we were saying okay, but could you increase this a little bit or 

4
00:00:06:29 --> 00:00:10:29
what if that was linked to another aspect of the simulation 

5
00:00:11:02 --> 00:00:15:08
and that kind of back and forth worked really well where you kind of separate 

6
00:00:15:11 --> 00:00:20:12
the use of a system from the person who has developed it 

7
00:00:20:15 --> 00:00:22:29
and kind of looking at it from a different perspective 

8
00:00:23:15 --> 00:00:26:01
can often lead to these surprising moments I guess 

9
00:00:26:04 --> 00:00:30:03
where you set up a system but then you let it go 

10
00:00:30:08 --> 00:00:32:13
and you let somebody else play with it.

