2
00:00:00:11 --> 00:00:04:13
Yeah, if something reminds you something or if it tells you a story, 

3
00:00:04:16 --> 00:00:06:04
then it’s a starting point.  

4
00:00:06:07 --> 00:00:08:07
It almost like an access door 

5
00:00:08:10 --> 00:00:12:11
into an abstract visual realm, 

6
00:00:12:18 --> 00:00:18:26
and I think that can be really nice as an starting point for a conversation.

