2
00:00:00:03 --> 00:00:03:18
And there was this moment when I went to a festival 

3
00:00:04:00 --> 00:00:06:12
and this artist had come from Japan,

4
00:00:06:15 --> 00:00:10:28
and he is like I'm using openframeworks and I had no idea.  

5
00:00:11:01 --> 00:00:15:17
I knew our friends were using it and I knew people 

6
00:00:15:20 --> 00:00:20:15
who were using it, but to meet somebody from really far away. 

7
00:00:20:18 --> 00:00:25:23
Or like the only time I was at a festival and this couple came up to me 

8
00:00:25:26 --> 00:00:31:03
and this guy was like I just want to say thank you for openFrameworks and 

9
00:00:31:06 --> 00:00:37:20
his girlfriend was like I hate you, like my boy friend spends all his time in front of the computer, you know. 

10
00:00:37:23 --> 00:00:41:10
So those were the things that like in the early days 

when I started to realize

11
00:00:41:13 --> 00:00:47:08
that this thing is having a life of its own 

and was spreading and going like really far.

