2
00:00:00:27 --> 00:00:05:23
And one of the things that I remember really vividly from that time, from those days was kind of 

3
00:00:05:26 --> 00:00:11:09
fighting with the administration in my department about programming 

4
00:00:11:12 --> 00:00:13:22
and especially something like C++, 

5
00:00:13:25 --> 00:00:18:04
which was a computer science type of language, 

6
00:00:18:07 --> 00:00:20:28
and I had already arguments with them where it was like, 

7
00:00:21:01 --> 00:00:25:09
artist don’t want to learn C++ and artists don’t want to learn how to code,

8
00:00:25:12 --> 00:00:27:04
but 

9
00:00:28:14 --> 00:00:31:05
the way that I countered that argument was by 

10
00:00:31:08 --> 00:00:34:20
creating this tool or helping create this tool 

11
00:00:34:23 --> 00:00:39:19
and working with students and the work that they were making was so amazing that 

12
00:00:39:22 --> 00:00:43:08
within a year or two there was no argument anymore.

