2
00:00:03:03 --> 00:00:06:17
Sometimes it doesn’t work, like sometimes I mess up, sometimes

3
00:00:06:20 --> 00:00:08:29
for whatever reason it just doesn’t look right, 

4
00:00:09:02 --> 00:00:12:20
but when it works, when it’s working, 

5
00:00:12:23 --> 00:00:16:16
I feel like time slows down.  I feel like 

6
00:00:16:24 --> 00:00:20:20
there is a crazy energy 

7
00:00:20:23 --> 00:00:24:17
that’s produced between myself and the audience and the stuff that’s happening 

8
00:00:24:20 --> 00:00:30:29
and I can’t think of any other part of any project that does that that. That one does it.

and I can’t think of any other part of any project that does that that. That one does it.

