2
00:00:01:07 --> 00:00:05:26
So we started to collaborate, and once we were working together when I was a student, 

3
00:00:05:29 --> 00:00:09:21
but when I graduated, we started to work together as a team, and 

4
00:00:09:24 --> 00:00:14:00
my first summer out of school was going to Arts Electronic, 

5
00:00:14:03 --> 00:00:18:06
so I graduated and then I was on an airplane and I was in Linz, Austria and then 

6
00:00:18:09 --> 00:00:21:16
suddenly I was immersed in a culture 

7
00:00:21:19 --> 00:00:25:02
that I had only read about

8
00:00:25:05 --> 00:00:29:27
and had only known these people

sort of virtually just by studying what they do 

9
00:00:30:00 --> 00:00:33:24
and then to go there and be part of that culture was really amazing.

