2
00:00:01:00 --> 00:00:03:26
No, it’s fucking boring. It’s really boring.  

3
00:00:03:29 --> 00:00:09:08
I do like solving problems.   

4
00:00:09:18 --> 00:00:13:17
There is something that happens when you are programming a lot 

5
00:00:13:20 --> 00:00:17:05
that there is almost things that you can do half asleep, 

6
00:00:17:08 --> 00:00:19:26
and there are certain patterns where you are like okay,

7
00:00:19:29 --> 00:00:24:16
my brain, there is like a muscle memory or like an algorithmic memory, my brain 

8
00:00:24:19 --> 00:00:27:13
like can take this idea, this thing  that 

9
00:00:27:16 --> 00:00:33:22
I knew how to do when I was smarter and can do it when I’m not so smart and that stuff I like,

10
00:00:34:18 --> 00:00:40:20
and I am really curious, 

there is a side of me that 

11
00:00:41:03 --> 00:00:45:21
digs algorithms and digs the approach that makes it faster.  

12
00:00:45:24 --> 00:00:49:24
Here is the thing that you could do that solves this problem, for sure, 

13
00:00:49:27 --> 00:00:54:19
but actually coding itself is not fun to watch. 

14
00:00:54:22 --> 00:00:59:20
It’s fun, if you’re with other people and you’re coding together that’s fine, 

15
00:00:59:23 --> 00:01:04:19
but it is like any activity where you are sitting in front of a computer, 

16
00:01:04:27 --> 00:01:09:17
it’s not easy to share.

