2
00:00:01:06 --> 00:00:03:13
I am super happy when I am with a group.  

3
00:00:03:16 --> 00:00:08:00
When I am working with people either that are similar to me in that 

4
00:00:08:03 --> 00:00:12:17
we can kind of jam about code things and relate like

5
00:00:12:20 --> 00:00:15:28
in terms of what we do and what our aesthetics are ,  

6
00:00:16:01 --> 00:00:21:05
when you are working with somebody like that, it’s great, because you can say one word 

7
00:00:21:08 --> 00:00:25:04
and the other person knows what you are talking about, 

so with Golan, 

8
00:00:25:22 --> 00:00:31:01
we say something and it’s like it’s immediate communication, a very high bandwidth, 

9
00:00:31:04 --> 00:00:36:03
and then alternatively, I really like working with people that have no idea what I am doing 

10
00:00:36:06 --> 00:00:38:27
but are really interested in 

11
00:00:39:02 --> 00:00:44:05
the kind of stuff that I can that intersect with what they do, so 

12
00:00:44:08 --> 00:00:47:01
working with a magician and thinking about how 

13
00:00:47:04 --> 00:00:52:06
magic relates to these kind of real-time systems 

14
00:00:52:09 --> 00:00:57:00
or working with a dancer, or working with singers or something like that.

